<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by Gilgamesch on 2/15/2014 6:28:26 PM -->
<GameData>
	<!--/////////Buildings***Gametext\\\\\\\\\\\\-->
<Language_en_US>
	
	<!--BUILDINGS-->
	
	
	<!-- Palace Extention - Science Wing, building-->
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PALACE_SCIENCE_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>Increases global [ICON_RESEARCH] Science</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PALACE_SCIENCE</Tag>
		<Text>Palace - Science Wing</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_PALACE_SCIENCE_TEXT</Tag>
		<Text>This part of your palace is dedicated to scientific discoveries.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PALACE_SCIENCE_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<Text>Significantly increases your Civilization's [ICON_RESEARCH] Science output.</Text>
	</Row>
	
	<!--BUILDING_HORSE_DERBY-->
<Row>
	<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HORSE_DERBY</Tag>
	<Text>Horse Derby</Text>
</Row>
<Row>
	<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_HORSE_DERBY_DESC</Tag>
	<Text>A derby is a type of horse race, named after the Derby Stakes, still run at Epsom Downs Racecourse in England.  It was in turn named for Edward Smith-Stanley, 12th Earl of Derby, who inaugurated the race in 1780.  The best-known example in the United States is the Kentucky Derby.</Text>
</Row>
<Row>
	<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_HORSE_DERBY_HELP</Tag>
	<Text>+6 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and +10 [ICON_GOLD] Gold from every [ICON_RES_HORSE] Horse worked by this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Requires 1 [ICON_RES_HORSE] Horses.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]You may build 1.</Text>
</Row>
<Row>
	<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_HORSE_DERBY_QUOTE</Tag>
	<Text>[NEWLINE][TAB][TAB]"When a jockey retires, he just becomes another little man."[NEWLINE][TAB][TAB] - Eddie Arcaro[NEWLINE][TAB]</Text>
</Row>
	<!--ANCIENT-->
	<Update>
		<Set Text="+2 [ICON_FOOD] Food from every Oasis."/>
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BAZAAR_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="+2 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science from Jungle tiles worked by this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have a Library."/>
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WAT_HELP" />
	</Update>
	

	<Update>
		<Set Text="Each source of [ICON_RES_FUR] Fur and [ICON_RES_IVORY] Ivory worked by this City produce +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have an improved source of [ICON_RES_HORSE] Horses, [ICON_RES_FUR] Fur, or [ICON_RES_IVORY] Ivory nearby."/>
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CIRCUS_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="+10% [ICON_FOOD] Food carried over after a [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizen is born."/>
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GRANARY_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="Each source of [ICON_RES_MARBLE] Marble worked by this City produce +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have an improved source of [ICON_RES_MARBLE] Marble, [ICON_RES_STONE] Stone, or [ICON_RES_JADE] Jade nearby.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must not be in Plains."/>
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_STONE_WORKS_HELP" />
	</Update>

	<!--CLASSICAL-->
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ABBEY</Tag>
		<Text>Abbey</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ABBEY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<Text>An abbey, or nunnery, is a Christian monastery or convent, under the government of an Abbot or an Abbess, who serves as the spiritual father or mother of the community. The term can also refer to an establishment which has long ceased to function as an abbey, but continues to carry the name—in some cases for centuries.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ABBEY_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>Each source of [ICON_RES_COTTON] Cotton, [ICON_RES_DYE] Dye, and [ICON_RES_SILK] Silk worked by this City produces +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have at least one of these resources improved nearby.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ABBEY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<Text>The Abbey increases the Faith in a city and provides a small boost to [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness. It also provides additional bonuses for many resources.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ARTILLERY_RANGE</Tag>
		<Text>Artillery Range</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ARTILLERY_RANGE_PEDIA</Tag>
		<Text>Atillery Ranges give seige weapon operators the ability to test their equipment and become proficient at it's use.  Commanders of Other ground based units also recieve training here so they know the capabilities of current ranged weaponry.  </Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ARTILLERY_RANGE_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>+15 [ICON_WAR] XP for all Siege and Archer [ICON_SILVER_FIST] Units.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ARTILLERY_RANGE_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<Text>The Artillery Range provides experience for Ranged [ICON_SILVER_FIST] Units built in the city. This experience can be used to give the units Promotions, making them more effective in battle.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="Each worked Lake tile provides +2 [ICON_FOOD] Food.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must be built next to a River or Lake." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FLOATING_GARDENS_HELP" />
	</Update>	
	<Update>
		<Set Text="+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production from each worked Forest tile." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LONGHOUSE_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="Each source of [ICON_RES_GOLD] Gold, [ICON_RES_SILVER] Silver, and [ICON_RES_GEMS] Gems worked by this City produces +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have at least one of these resources mined nearby." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MINT_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="+1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science per 2 [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizens in this City." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PAPER_MAKER_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="Each sorce of [ICON_RES_HORSE] Horse or [ICON_RES_TRUFFLES] Truffles worked by this City produces +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+15 XP for all Mounted Units.[NEWLINE]Increase [ICON_PLAGUE] Plague by +1.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have an improved source of [ICON_RES_HORSE] Horse or [ICON_RES_TRUFFLES] Truffles nearby."/>
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_STABLE_HELP" />
	</Update>











	<!--<Update>
			<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WORKSHOP_STRATEGY" />
			<Set Text="Greatly increases [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production in this City."/>
		</Update>-->

	<!--MEDIEVAL-->
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CITY_CLOCK</Tag>
		<Text>City Clock</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CITY_CLOCK_PEDIA</Tag>
		<Text>A City Clock is a tower specifically built with one or more (often four) clock faces. Clock towers can be either freestanding or part of a church or municipal building such as a town hall. Some clock towers are not true clock towers having had their clock faces added to an already existing building. These 'false' clock towers should not be confused with true clock towers but are still significant buildings.  The mechanism inside the tower is known as a turret clock. It often marks the hour (and sometimes segments of an hour) by sounding large bells or chimes, sometimes playing simple musical phrases or tunes.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CITY_CLOCK_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<Text>The City Clock provides a one-time boost to gold. Use it to boost your economy.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CITY_CLOCK_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>Provides a one-time instance of +360 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.</Text>
	</Row>





	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SEWER_SYSTEM</Tag>
		<Text>Sewer System [ICON_HEALTH]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SEWER_SYSTEM_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>Sewer Systems dramatically increase the health of a City population by shuttling waste away from the people and their drainking water.  The first sewer system dates back to the year 1370 when the first underground system was constructed under "rue Montmartre" in Paris. Since then consecutive French governments have enlarged the system to cover the City's population.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SEWER_SYSTEM_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<Text>10% of [ICON_FOOD] Food is carried over after a new [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizen is born.[NEWLINE]Increase [ICON_HEALTH] Health by +1.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have a Granary.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_REGIONAL_FAIR</Tag>
		<Text>Regional Fair</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_REGIONAL_FAIR_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>A regional fair is a trade event hosted by a n organization(usually town, City, or corporation), that seeks to create greater commerce through a gathering of like minded merchants or professionals.  Starting in the medieval era as a way for nobles and lords to draw merchants to their areas, it continues today in forms varrying from like minded individuals sharing passions, to super corporations seeking to incite hype among consumers.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_REGIONAL_FAIR_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>+1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold from [ICON_GREAT_MERCHANT] Merchant Specialist in every City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]You may build up to 1.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JEWELRY_STORE</Tag>
		<Text>Jewelry Store</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JEWELRY_STORE_PEDIA</Tag>
		<Text>A jewelry store or jeweler is a retail business specializing in selling jewelry.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JEWELRY_STORE_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>Each souce of [ICON_RES_GOLD] Gold or [ICON_RES_COPPER] Copper worked by this City produces +3 [ICON_GOLD] Gold. Each source of [ICON_RES_SILVER] Silver or [ICON_RES_GEMS] Gems worked by this City produces +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have a Mint.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JEWELRY_STORE_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<Text>The Jeweler significantly improves the gold produced by precious metals.  Build it in cities with more than one of these metals for the best results.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TOWN_HALL</Tag>
		<Text>Town Hall</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TOWN_HALL_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>In local government, a City hall, town hall or (more rarely) a municipal building or civic centre, is the chief administrative building of a City town or other municipality. It usually houses the City or town council, its associated departments, and their employees. It also usually functions as the base of the mayor of a City, town, borough, or county.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]By convention, until the mid 19th-century, a single large open chamber (or 'hall') formed an integral part of the building housing the council. The hall may be used for council meetings and other significant events. This large chamber, the 'town hall', (and its later variant 'City hall') has become synonymous with the whole building, and with the administrative body housed in it. The terms 'council chambers', 'municipal building' or variants may be used locally in preference to 'town hall' if no such large hall is present within the building.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TOWN_HALL_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<Text>+1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold for every 4 [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizens in this City</Text>
	</Row>

	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GUILD_HALL</Tag>
		<Text>Guild Hall</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GUILD_HALL_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>A guild is an association of craftsmen in a particular trade. The earliest guilds were formed as confraternities of workers. They were organized in a manner something between a trade union, a cartel and a secret society. They often depended on grants of letters patent by an authority or monarch to enforce the flow of trade to their self-employed members, and to retain ownership of tools and the supply of materials. A lasting legacy of traditional guilds are the guildhalls constructed and used as meeting places.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GUILD_HALL_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production from [ICON_GREAT_ENGINNER] Engineer Specialist in this City.[NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold from Merchant Specialist in this City.[NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture from Artist Specialist in this City.[NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science from Scientist Specialist in this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]DOES NOT WORK YET...SORRY :(.</Text>
	</Row>
	
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PUBLISHING_HOUSE</Tag>
		<Text>Publishing House</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PUBLISHING_HOUSE_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>Publishing is the process of production and dissemination of literature or information for public view. In some cases authors may be their own publishers, meaning: originators and developers of content also provide media to deliver and display the content.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PUBLISHING_HOUSE_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<Text>[ICON_CULTURE] Culture Cost for aquiring new tiles reduced by 33% in this City.</Text>
	</Row>

	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FOUNDRY</Tag>
		<Text>Foundry</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FOUNDRY_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>A foundry is a factory that produces metal castings. Metals are cast into shapes by melting them into a liquid, pouring the metal in a mold, and removing the mold material or casting after the metal has solidified as it cools. The most common metals processed are aluminum and cast iron. However, other metals, such as steel, magnesium, copper, tin, and zinc, are also used to produce castings in foundries.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FOUNDRY_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>Requires 1 [ICON_RES_IRON] Iron.[NEWLINE]City must have a Forge.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RACE_TRACK</Tag>
		<Text>Race Track</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RACE_TRACK_PEDIA</Tag>
		<Text>Horse racing is an equestrian sport that has a long history. Archaeological records indicate that horse racing occurred in ancient Babylon, Syria, and Egypt. Thoroughbred racing was, and is, popular with the aristocrats and royalty of British society, earning it the title "Sport of Kings."There are three major types of racing: flat racing, steeplechasing (racing over jumps), and harness racing, where horses trot or pace while pulling a driver in a sulky. A major part of horse racing's economic importance lies in the gambling associated with it, an activity that in 2008 generated a world-wide market worth around US$115 billion.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RACE_TRACK_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>Each source of [ICON_RES_HORSE] Horse worked by this City produces +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have an improved source of Horse nearby.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RACE_TRACK_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<Text>The Race Track increases the [ICON_GOLD] Gold output of [ICON_RES_HORSE] Horse. It also increases a civilization's [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PRISON</Tag>
		<Text>Prison [ICON_ORDER][ICON_PLAGUE]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PRISON_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>A prison is a place in which people are physically confined and, usually, deprived of a range of personal freedoms.  Imprisonment or incarceration is a legal penalty that may be imposed by the state for the commission of a crime.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PRISON_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<Text>Increases this city's [ICON_STRENGTH] Hit Points by +25.[NEWLINE]Increase [ICON_PLAGUE] Plague by +1.[NEWLINE]Increase [ICON_ORDER] Order by +4.</Text>
	</Row>
	
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MISSIONARY_CHURCH</Tag>
		<Text>Missionary Church [ICON_RELIGION]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MISSIONARY_CHURCH_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>A Missionary Church is a church whose general purpose is to spread the religious values and ideals from one area to another.  While Missionary Churches are generally thought of as crossing borders or oceans, they also spread shorter distances such as across town or state.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MISSIONARY_CHURCH_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>Increases [ICON_PEACE] Religious Pressure in this City by 15%.[NEWLINE]Construct this building by purchasing it with [ICON_PEACE] Faith.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have an Abbey.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RANCH</Tag>
		<Text>Ranch</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RANCH_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>A ranch is an area of landscape, including various structures, given primarily to the practice of ranching, the practice of raising grazing livestock such as cattle or sheep for meat or wool. The word most often applies to livestock-raising operations in the western United States and Canada, though there are ranches in other areas. People who own or operate a ranch are called stockgrowers or ranchers. Ranching is also a method used to raise less common livestock such as elk, American bison or even ostrich, emu, and alpacas.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RANCH_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<Text>Each source of [ICON_RES_HORSE] Horse worked by this City produces +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have an improved source of [ICON_RES_HORSE] Horse, [ICON_RES_COW] Cow, or [ICON_RES_SHEEP] Sheep nearby.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DECLARATION_OF_INDEPENDENCE</Tag>
		<Text>Declaration of Independence</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_DECLARATION_OF_INDEPENDENCE_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>Declaration of Independence is an assertion of the independence of an aspiring state or states. Such places are usually declared from part or all of the territory of another nation or failed nation, or are breakaway territories from within the larger state. Not all declarations of independence were successful and resulted in independence for these regions.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<!-- added BNW -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_DECLARATION_OF_INDEPENDENCE_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>1 free [ICON_RESEARCH] Technology and one extra [ICON_DIPLOMAT] vote in the world congress.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Must have at least 3 Publishing Houses in your empire.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_DECLARATION_OF_INDEPENDENCE_QUOTE</Tag>
		<Text>[NEWLINE][TAB][TAB]"Experience hath shown, that even under the best forms (of government) those entrusted with power have, in time, and by slow operations, perverted it into tyranny."[NELWINE][TAB][TAB] - Thomas Jefferson[NEWLINE][TAB]</Text>
	</Row>
	<!--<Row>
			<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HORSE_DERBY</Tag>
			<Text>Horse Derby</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_HORSE_DERBY_DESC</Tag>
			<Text>A derby is a type of horse race, named after the Derby Stakes, still run at Epsom Downs Racecourse in England.  It was in turn named for Edward Smith-Stanley, 12th Earl of Derby, who inaugurated the race in 1780.  The best-known example in the United States is the Kentucky Derby.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_HORSE_DERBY_HELP</Tag>
			<Text>+6 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and +10 [ICON_GOLD] Gold from every [ICON_RES_HORSE] Horse worked by this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Requires 1 [ICON_RES_HORSE] Horses.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]You may build 1.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_HORSE_DERBY_QUOTE</Tag>
			<Text>[NEWLINE][TAB][TAB]"When a jockey retires, he just becomes another little man."[NEWLINE][TAB][TAB] - Eddie Arcaro[NEWLINE][TAB]</Text>
		</Row>-->
	
	<!--<Row>
			<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_POLICE_STATION</Tag>
			<Text>Police Station</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_POLICE_STATION_DESC</Tag>
			<Text>A police station or station house is a building which serves to accommodate police officers and other members of staff. These buildings often contain offices and accommodation for personnel and vehicles, along with locker rooms, temporary holding cells and interview/interrogation rooms.</Text>
		</Row>-->
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_OIL_REFINERY</Tag>
		<Text>Oil Refinery [ICON_PLAGUE]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_OIL_REFINERY_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>An oil refinery or petroleum refinery is an industrial process plant where crude oil is processed and refined into more useful petroleum products, such as gasoline, diesel fuel, asphalt base, heating oil, kerosene, and liquefied natural gas.  Oil refineries are typically large sprawling industrial complexes with extensive piping running throughout, carrying streams of fluids between large chemical processing units. In many ways, oil refineries use much of the technology of, and can be thought of as types of chemical plants. The crude oil feedstock has typically been processed by an oil production plant. There is usually an oil depot (tank farm) at or near an oil refinery for storage of bulk liquid products.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_OIL_REFINERY_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>Provides 3 [ICON_RES_DIESEL] Diesel and [ICON_RES_KEROSENE] Kerosene.[NEWLINE]Requries one resource of [COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Oil[ENDCOLOR] to build.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Each source of [ICON_RES_OIL] Oil worked by this city produces +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE]Increase [ICON_PLAGUE] Plague by +2.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have an improved source of [ICON_RES_OIL] Oil nearby.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NAVAL_BASE</Tag>
		<Text>Naval Base [SILVER_FIST]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NAVAL_BASE_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>A naval base (military port) is a military base, where warships and naval ships are deployed when they have no mission at sea or want to restock. Usually ships may also perform some minor repairs.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NAVAL_BASE_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<Text>+15 [ICON_WAR] XP for all Sea [SILVER_FIST] units built in this City.[NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Requires a Seaport in this City.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AQUARIUM</Tag>
		<Text>Aquarium</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AQUARIUM_PEDIA</Tag>
		<Text>An aquarium is a vivarium consisting of at least one transparent side in which water-dwelling plants or animals are kept. Fishkeepers use aquaria to keep fish, invertebrates, amphibians, marine mammals, turtles, and aquatic plants.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AQUARIUM_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<Text>The Aquarium increases the science output of an improved sea resource. It also increases a civilization's [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AQUARIUM_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>+1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science from Sea Resources worked by this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have at least one Sea Resource improved nearby.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must be built on the coast.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SUPERMARKET</Tag>
		<Text>Supermarket [ICON_HEALTH]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SUPERMARKET_PEDIA</Tag>
		<Text>A supermarket, a form of grocery store, is a self-service store offering a wide variety of food and household merchandise, organized into departments. It is larger in size and has a wider selection than a traditional grocery store and it is smaller than a hypermarket or superstore.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SUPERMARKET_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>City must have a Granary.[NEWLINE]Increase [ICON_HEALTH] Health by +1.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SUPERMARKET_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<Text>The supermarket greatly increases the food intake of a city.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_INDUSTRIAL_SHIPYARD</Tag>
		<Text>Industrial Shipyard</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_INDUSTRIAL_SHIPYARD_PEDIA</Tag>
		<Text>Shipyards and dockyards are places which repair and build ships. These can be yachts, military vessels, cruise liners or other cargo or passenger ships. Dockyards are sometimes more associated with maintenance and basing activities than shipyards, which are sometimes associated more with initial construction. The terms are routinely used interchangeably, in part because the evolution of dockyards and shipyards has often caused them to change or merge roles.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_INDUSTRIAL_SHIPYARD_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>Required for Battleship, Carrier, Supercarrier, Missile Cruiser, Nuclear Submarine, and Submarine production.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Requires 2 [ICON_RES_OIL] Oil for construction.[NEWLINE]City must have a Seaport and must not contain an Aircraft Plant or an Auto Plant.</Text>
	</Row>
	
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AUTO_PLANT</Tag>
		<Text>Auto Plant</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AUTO_PLANT_PEDIA</Tag>
		<Text>Auto plants are a type of factory whose sole purpose is to manufacture and assemble automotives.  While a laborous process at first, the invention of the Assembly Line revolutioned the auto industry, as well as the rest of the manufacturing world, by cutting assembly time and costs down to a mere fraction.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AUTO_PLANT_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>Required for Tank, Panzer, Modern Armor, and Rocket Artillery production.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Requires 2 [ICON_RES_OIL] Oil for construction.[NEWLINE]City must have a Factory and must not contain an Aircraft Plant or Industrial Shipyard.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RECYCLING_PLANT</Tag>
		<Text>Recycling Plant [ICON_PLAGUE]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RECYCLING_PLANT_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>Recycling involves processing used materials (waste) into new products to prevent waste of potentially useful materials, reduce the consumption of fresh raw materials, reduce energy usage, reduce air pollution (from incineration) and water pollution (from landfilling) by reducing the need for "conventional" waste disposal, and lower greenhouse gas emissions as compared to virgin production.  Recycling is a key component of modern waste reduction and is the third component of the "Reduce, Reuse, Recycle" waste hierarchy.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RECYCLING_PLANT_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>Each source of [ICON_RES_MARBLE] Marble or [ICON_RES_SILK] Silk worked by this City produces +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE]Increase [ICON_PLAGUE] Plague by +1.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have an improved source of one of these resources nearby.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MASS_TRANSIT</Tag>
		<Text>Mass Transit [ICON_PLAGUE]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MASS_TRANSIT_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>Public transport (also public transportation, public transit, or mass transit) is a shared passenger transportation service which is available for use by the general public, as distinct from modes such as Taxicab and car pooling which are not shared by strangers without private arrangement.  Public transport modes include buses, trolleybuses, trams and trains, 'rapid transit' (metro/subways/undergrounds etc) and ferries. InterCity public transport is dominated by airlines, coaches, and interCity rail. High-speed rail networks are being developed in many parts of the world.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<!-- BNW added -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MASS_TRANSIT_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<Text>Increases [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness in this City and gives a little boost to [ICON_TOURISM] touristic.[NEWLINE]Increase [ICON_PLAGUE] Plague by +2.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DRUG_STORE</Tag>
		<Text>Drug Store [ICON_HEALTH]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DRUG_STORE_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>Pharmacy is the health profession that links the health sciences with the chemical sciences and it is charged with ensuring the safe and effective use of pharmaceutical drugs.  The scope of pharmacy practice includes more traditional roles such as compounding and dispensing medications, and it also includes more modern services related to health care, including clinical services, reviewing medications for safety and efficacy, and providing drug information. Pharmacists, therefore, are the experts on drug therapy and are the primary health professionals who optimize medication use to provide patients with positive health outcomes.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DRUG_STORE_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<Text>Increases [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness in this City.[NEWLINE]Increase [ICON_PLAGUE] Health by +2</Text>
	</Row>

	!<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PUBLIC_BATHS</Tag>
		<Text>Public Baths [ICON_HEALTH]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PUBLIC_BATHS_PEDIA</Tag>
		<Text>Public baths originated from a communal need for cleanliness. The term public may confuse some people, as some types of public baths are restricted depending on membership, gender, religious affiliation, or other reasons. In ancient times public bathing included saunas, massages and relaxation therapies. Members of the society considered it as a place to meet and socialize. Public bathing could be compared to the spa of modern times.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PUBLIC_BATHS_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>City must be built next to a River or Lake.[NEWLINE]Increase [ICON_HEALTH] Health by +1.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PUBLIC_BATHS_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<Text>The Public Baths increases a civilization's [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness. It can only be constructed in a city next to a river or lake.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AIRBASE</Tag>
		<Text>Airbase</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AIRBASE_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>An airbase is a military airfield that provides basing and support of military aircraft.  They are different from civilian airports in that they do not provide for large volume of passenger transits, and cargo handling is not processed by the customs and immigration facilities. Some military air forces combine use of civilian airports with the hosting of military units.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AIRBASE_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<Text>+15 [ICON_WAR] XP for all Air [ICON_SILVER_FIST] units built in this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have an Aircraft Plant.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AIRCRAFT_PLANT</Tag>
		<Text>Aircraft Plant</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AIRCRAFT_PLANT_PEDIA</Tag>
		<Text>Aircraft plants are a type of factory whose sole purpose is to manufacture and assemble aircraft.  Making use of the Assembly Line and a dedicated parts industry, the aircraft plant is able to mass produce military aircraft for the war effort, and commercial aircraft during peacetime.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AIRCRAFT_PLANT_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>Required for Fighter, Bomber, B-17, Jet Fighter, and Helicopter Gunship production.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Requires 2 [ICON_RES_OIL] Oil for construction.[NEWLINE]City must have a Factory and must not contain an Auto Plant or Industrial Shipyard.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DOCK</Tag>
		<Text>Dock [ICON_PLAGUE]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DOCK_PEDIA</Tag>
		<Text>A dock is a human-made structure or group of structures involved in the handling of boats or ships, usually on or close to a shore. The world's oldest known dock at Lothal (2400 BCE) was located away from the main current to avoid deposition of silt. Modern oceanographers have observed that the Harappans must have possessed great knowledge relating to tides in order to build such a dock on the ever-shifting course of the Sabarmati, as well as exemplary hydrography and maritime engineering. This was the earliest known dock found in the world, equipped to berth and service ships. It is speculated that Lothal engineers studied tidal movements, and their effects on brick-built structures, since the walls are of kiln-burnt bricks.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DOCK_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>+1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold from water tiles worked by this City.[NEWLINE]Increase [ICON_PLAGUE] Plague by +1.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DOCK_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<Text>The Dock can only be constructed in a city next to a coastal tile. It increases the [ICON_GOLD] Gold output for water tiles.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SHAMAN_HUT</Tag>
		<Text>Shaman's Hut</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SHAMAN_HUT_PEDIA</Tag>
		<Text>A shaman is a person regarded as having access to, and influence in, the world of benevolent and malevolent spirits, who typically enters a trance state during a ritual, and practices divination and healing.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SHAMAN_HUT_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>Each source of [ICON_RES_WINE] Wine, [ICON_RES_INCENSE] Incense or Wild Berries worked by this City produces +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Provides one free Shaman [ICON_SILVER_FIST] Unit.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SHAMAN_HUT_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<Text>The Shaman's Hut provides [ICON_GOLD] Gold for resources used in religious contexts.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CHEMICAL_PLANT</Tag>
		<Text>Chemical Plant [ICON_PLAGUE]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CHEMICAL_PLANT_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>A chemical plant is an industrial process plant that manufactures (or otherwise processes) chemicals, usually on a large scale. The general objective of a chemical plant is to create new material wealth via the chemical or biological transformation and or separation of materials.  Chemical plants use special equipment, units, and technology in the processes. Other kinds of plants, such as polymer, pharmaceutical, food, and some beverage production facilities, power plants, oil refineries or other refineries, natural gas processing and biochemical plants, water and wastewater treatment, and pollution control equipment use many technologies which have similarities to chemical plant technology such as fluid systems. Some would consider an oil refinery or a pharmaceutical or polymer manufacturer to be effectively a chemical plant.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CHEMICAL_PLANT_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<Text>Each source of [ICON_RES_DYE] Dye worked by this City produces +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and +2 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science. Each source of [ICON_RES_INCENSE] Incense worked by this City produces +2 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science.[NEWLINE]Increase [ICON_PLAGUE] by +2[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have at least one of these resources improved nearby.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TEXTILE_MILL</Tag>
		<Text>Textile Mill</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TEXTILE_MILL_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>Textile manufacturing is a major industry. It is based in the conversion of three types of fibre into yarn, then fabric, then textiles. These are then fabricated into clothes or other artifacts. Cotton remains the most important natural fibre, so is treated in depth. There are many variable processes available at the spinning and fabric-forming stages coupled with the complexities of the finishing and colouration processes to the production of a wide ranges of products. There remains a large industry that uses hand techniques to achieve the same results.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TEXTILE_MILL_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<Text>Each source of [ICON_RES_COTTON] Cotton, [ICON_RES_FUR] Fur, and [ICON_RES_IVORY] Ivory worked by this City produce +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have at least one of these resources improved nearby.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FOOD_PROCESSING_PLANT</Tag>
		<Text>Food Processing Plant [ICON_HEALTH]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FOOD_PROCESSING_PLANT_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>Food processing is the set of methods and techniques used to transform raw ingredients into food or to transform food into other forms for consumption by humans or animals either in the home or by the food processing industry. Food processing typically takes clean, harvested crops or butchered animal products and uses these to produce attractive, marketable and often long shelf-life food products. Similar processes are used to produce animal feed.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FOOD_PROCESSING_PLANT_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<Text>Each source of [ICON_RES_SPICES] Spices or [ICON_RES_SALT] Salt worked by this City produces +2 [ICON_FOOD] Food and +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold. Each source of [ICON_RES_WINE] Wine worked by this City produces +2 [ICON_FOOD] Food.[NEWLINE]Increase [ICON_HEALTH] Health by +1.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have an improved source of one of these resources nearby.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_INDUSTRIAL_WAREHOUSE</Tag>
		<Text>Industrial Warehouse</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_INDUSTRIAL_WAREHOUSE_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>A warehouse is a commercial building for storage of goods. Warehouses are used by manufacturers, importers, exporters, wholesalers, transport businesses, customs, etc. They are usually large plain buildings in industrial areas of cities and towns. They usually have loading docks to load and unload goods from trucks. Sometimes warehouses load and unload goods directly from railways, airports, or seaports. They often have cranes and forklifts for moving goods, which are usually placed on ISO standard pallets loaded into pallet racks.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_INDUSTRIAL_WAREHOUSE_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<Text>Each source of [ICON_RES_SUGAR] Sugar, [ICON_RES_CITRUS] Citrus, or [ICON_RES_TRUFFLES] Truffles worked by this City produces +2 [ICON_FOOD] Food and +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have an improved source of one of theses resources nearby.</Text>
	</Row>
	
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_INTERSTATE_HIGHWAY_SYSTEM</Tag>
		<Text>Interstate Highway System [ICON_PLAGUE]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_INTERSTATE_HIGHWAY_SYSTEM_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>The Dwight D. Eisenhower National System of Interstate and Defense Highways, commonly called the Interstate Highway System or Interstate Freeway System, and colloquially abbreviated "the Interstate", is a network of limited-access roadways (also called freeways or expressways) in the United States. It is named for President Dwight D. Eisenhower, who championed its formation. As of 2006, the system has a total length of 46,876 miles (75,440 km), making it both the largest highway system in the world and the largest public works project in history.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_INTERSTATE_HIGHWAY_SYSTEM_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>+50% [ICON_GOLD] Gold from [ICON_CONNECTED] Trade Routes.[NEWLINE]Increase [ICON_PLAGUE] by +2.[NEWLINE]You may build up to 1.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SMALLPOX_ERADICATION</Tag>
		<Text>Smallpox Eradication [ICON_HEALTH]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_SMALLPOX_ERADICATION_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>The smallpox vaccine was the first successful vaccine to be developed. The process of vaccination was discovered by Edward Jenner in 1796, who acted upon his observation that milkmaids who caught the cowpox virus did not catch smallpox.  Prior to widespread vaccination, mortality rates in individuals with smallpox were high—up to 35% in some cases.  It is estimated that the virus killed 300 million people in the 20th century alone.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_SMALLPOX_ERADICATION_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>+1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold from [ICON_CITIZEN] Specialists in every City.[NEWLINE]Provides +4 [ICON_HEALTH] Health.[NEWLINE]+4 [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_SMALLPOX_ERADICATION_QUOTE</Tag>
		<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]"I hope that some day the practice of producing cowpox in human beings will spread over the world - when that day comes, there will be no more smallpox" (Edward Jenner, 200 years before Smallpox Eradication)</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MEGACHURCH</Tag>
		<Text>Megachurch</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MEGACHURCH_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>A megachurch is a church having 2,000 or more attendees for a typical weekly service. The Hartford Institute's database lists more than 1,300 such Protestant churches in the United States. According to that data, approximately 50 churches on the list have attendance ranging from 10,000 to 47,000.  While 3,000 individual Roman Catholic parishes (churches) have 2,000 or more attendants for an average Sunday Mass, these churches are not seen as part of the megachurch movement.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Globally, these large congregations are a significant development in Protestant Christianity. While generally associated with the United States, the phenomenon has spread worldwide. In 2007, five of the ten largest Protestant churches were in South Korea.  Most megachurches tend to be evangelical or Pentecostal, and are often semi-independent from the major Christian denominations.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The megachurch movement, with a large number of local congregants who return on a weekly basis, is usually thought to have begun in the 1950s.  There have been large churches earlier in history, but they were considerably rarer. Examples include Charles Spurgeon's Baptist Metropolitan Tabernacle in London which attracted 5,000 weekly for years in the late 19th century, and religious broadcaster Aimee Semple McPherson's Angelus Temple in Los Angeles, which was similarly large.  The current largest megachurch in the world is the Yoido Full Gospel Church found in South Korea, with 830,000 members as of 2007.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MEGACHURCH_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>City must have a Missionary Church.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MOVIE_THEATRE</Tag>
		<Text>Movie Theatre</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MOVIE_THEATRE_PEDIA</Tag>
		<Text>A movie theater (also called a movie house, film theater, film house, picture theater or cinema) is a venue, usually a building, for viewing motion pictures ("movies" or "films"). Most but not all movie theaters are commercial operations catering to the general public, who attend by purchasing a ticket. The movie is projected with a movie projector onto a large projection screen at the front of the auditorium. Some movie theaters are now equipped for digital cinema projection, removing the need to create and transport a physical film print.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MOVIE_THEATRE_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>It cannot provide more [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness than there are [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizens in a city. City must have a Stadium.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MOVIE_THEATRE_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<Text>A Movie Theatre is a Modern-era building which increases the [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness of your entire empire, not just the city in which it is constructed. The city must already possess a Stadium before it can construct a Movie Theatre.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CRYSTAL_CATHEDRAL</Tag>
		<Text>Crystal Cathedral</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_CRYSTAL_CATHEDRAL_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>The Crystal Cathedral is a Protestant Christian Church in the City of Garden Grove, in Orange County, California, United States. The prominent architect Philip Johnson designed the main sanctuary building, which was constructed using over 10,000 rectangular panes of glass and its sanctuary seats 2,736 people.  The rectangular panes of glass are not bolted to the structure; instead they are glued to it using a silicone-based glue. This and other measures are intended to allow the building to withstand an earthquake of magnitude 8.0.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The name "Crystal Cathedral" is merely an alliterative colloquialism and does not mean that the church is a cathedral in the sense of being a church where there is a bishop's official seat; the Reformed Church in America is governed by elders. Nor is the church made of crystal. The church is a Southern California architectural landmark.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_CRYSTAL_CATHEDRAL_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>+25% [ICON_CULTURE] Culture generation Empire Wide.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+2 [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness per City.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_CRYSTAL_CATHEDRAL_QUOTE</Tag>
		<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]"You can educate yourself right out of a relationship with God." (Tammy Faye Bakker)</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TELEVISION</Tag>
		<Text>Television</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TELEVISION_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>Television (TV) is a widely used telecommunication medium for transmitting and receiving moving images that are either monochromatic ("black and white") or color, usually accompanied by sound. "Television" may also refer specifically to a television set, television programming or television transmission.  Commercially available since the late 1920s, the television set has become common in homes, businesses and institutions, particularly as a source of entertainment and news. Since the 1970s the availability of video cassettes, laserdiscs, DVDs and now Blu-ray Discs, have resulted in the television set frequently being used for viewing recorded as well as broadcast material.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TELEVISION_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<Text>Increases [ICON_GOLD] Gold and [ICON_RESEARCH] Science in this City.</Text>
	</Row>-
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SHOPPING_MALL</Tag>
		<Text>Shopping Mall</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SHOPPING_MALL_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>A shopping mall, shopping centre, shopping precinct or simply mall is one or more buildings forming a complex of shops representing merchandisers, with interconnecting walkways enabling visitors to easily walk from unit to unit, along with a parking area – a modern, indoor version of the traditional marketplace.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Modern "car-friendly" strip malls developed from the 1920s, and shopping malls corresponded with the rise of suburban living in many parts of the Western World, especially the United States, after World War II. From early on, the design tended to be inward-facing, with malls following theories of how customers could best be enticed in a controlled environment. Similar, the concept of a mall having one or more "anchor" or "big box" stores was pioneered early, with individual stores or smaller-scale chain stores intended to benefit from the shoppers attracted by the big stores.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SHOPPING_MALL_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<Text>+30 [ICON_GOLD] Gold for every 1 [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizens in this City.</Text>
	</Row>

	<!-- 
		<Row>
			<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AIRPORT</Tag>
			<Text>Airport</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AIRPORT_DESC</Tag>
			<Text>An airport is a location where aircraft such as fixed-wing aircraft, helicopters, and blimps takeoff and land. Aircraft may be stored or maintained at an airport. An airport consists of at least one surface such as a runway for a plane to takeoff and land, a helipad, or water for takeoffs and landings, and often includes buildings such as control towers, hangars and terminal buildings.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AIRPORT_STRATEGY</Tag>
			<Text>Allows the Airlifting of 3 units a turn from this City.</Text>
		</Row> -->
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BIOTECH_INDUSTRIAL_PARK</Tag>
		<Text>Biotech Industrial Park</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_BIOTECH_INDUSTRIAL_PARK_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>Biotechnology industrial park (BIP, also called Bio-industrial park, Eco-industrial Clusters, bioincubators) is a special form of industrial park that specializes in biotechnology.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_BIOTECH_INDUSTRIAL_PARK_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>Increases [ICON_GOLD] Gold and [ICON_RESEARCH] Science in this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]You may build up to 1.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_INDUSTRIAL_ROBOTICS</Tag>
		<Text>Industrial Robotics</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_INDUSTRIAL_ROBOTICS_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>An industrial robot is officially defined by ISO as an automatically controlled, reprogrammable, multipurpose manipulator programmable in three or more axes. The field of robotics may be more practically defined as the study, design and use of robot systems for manufacturing (a top-level definition relying on the prior definition of robot).  Typical applications of robots include welding, painting, assembly, pick and place, packaging and palletizing, product inspection, and testing, all accomplished with high endurance, speed, and precision.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_INDUSTRIAL_ROBOTICS_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>Each source of [ICON_RES_ALUMINUM] Aluminum worked by this City produces +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold. Each source of [ICON_RES_COAL] Coal worked by this City produces +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have a Factory.</Text>
	</Row>
	
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ADVANCED_AIRCRAFT_PLANT</Tag>
		<Text>Advanced Aircraft Plant</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ADVANCED_AIRCRAFT_PLANT_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>Advanced Aircraft plants are a type of factory whose sole purpose is to manufacture and assemble advanced aircraft.  Making use of the Assembly Line and a dedicated parts industry, the advanced aircraft plant is able to mass produce military advanced aircraft for the war effort, and advanced commercial aircraft during peacetime.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ADVANCED_AIRCRAFT_PLANT_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<Text>Required for Stealth Fighter, Stealth Bomber, Unmanned Aircraft, Hypersonic Interceptor, Hypersonic Bomber, and Stealth Gunship production.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have an Aircraft Plant. Requires 2 [ICON_RES_ALUMINUM] Aluminum.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GPS_SATELLITES</Tag>
		<Text>GPS Satellites [ICON_RES_MANPOWER]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_GPS_SATELLITES_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>A GPS satellite is a satellite used by the NAVSTAR Global Positioning System (GPS). The first satellite in the system, Navstar 1, was launched February 22, 1978. The GPS satellite constellation is operated by the 50th Space Wing of the United States Air Force.  GPS Satellites increase commerce and allow accurate control and targeting of defense systems.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_GPS_SATELLITES_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>+20% [ICON_GOLD] Gold from [ICON_CONNECTED] Trade Routes.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Defensive Buildings in all Cities are 50% more effective.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_GPS_SATELLITES_QUOTE</Tag>
		<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]"The bottom line -- GPS is absolutely critical to our nation's economic well being." (Michael Shaw)</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CURE_FOR_CANCER</Tag>
		<Text>Cure for Cancer [ICON_RES_MANPOWER][ICON_HEALTH]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_CURE_FOR_CANCER_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>Starting in the mid-1990s, the emphasis in clinical cancer research shifted towards therapies derived from biotechnology research, such as immunotherapy and gene therapy.  With the Human Genome mapped and all cancers classified, research shifted to the genetic causes of these diseases until specific gene therapies could be created for each of them, and tailored to an individual's specific genetics.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_CURE_FOR_CANCER_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>+5 [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness in each City.[NEWLINE]Increase [ICON_HEALTH] Health by +4.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_CURE_FOR_CANCER_QUOTE</Tag>
		<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]It has recently been discovered that research causes cancer in rats.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CELL_TOWERS</Tag>
		<Text>Cell Towers</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CELL_TOWERS_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>A cell site(aka cell tower) is a term used to describe a site where antennas and electronic communications equipment are placed on a radio mast or tower to create a cell in a cellular network. A cell site is composed of a tower or other elevated structure for mounting antennas, and one or more sets of transmitter/receivers transceivers, digital signal processors, control electronics, a GPS receiver for timing (for CDMA2000 or IS-95 systems), regular and backup electrical power sources, and sheltering.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CELL_TOWERS_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>It cannot provide more [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness than there are [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizens in a city. City must have a Stadium.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SERVER_FARM</Tag>
		<Text>Server Farm</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SERVER_FARM_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>A server farm or server cluster is a collection of computer servers usually maintained by an enterprise to accomplish server needs far beyond the capability of one machine. Server farms often have backup servers, which can take over the function of primary servers in the event of a primary server failure. Server farms are typically co-located with the network switches and/or routers which enable communication between the different parts of the cluster and the users of the cluster. The computers, routers, power supplies, and related electronics are typically mounted on 19-inch racks in a server room or data center.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SERVER_FARM_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>+1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science for every 2 [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizens in this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have a Research Laboratory.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<!--BNW overworked-->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_INTERNETX</Tag>
		<Text>Internet [ICON_RES_MANPOWER]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_INTERNETX_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>The origins of the Internet reach back to the 1960s with both private and United States military research into robust, fault-tolerant, and distributed computer networks. The funding of a new U.S. backbone by the National Science Foundation, as well as private funding for other commercial backbones, led to worldwide participation in the development of new networking technologies, and the merger of many networks. The commercialization of what was by then an international network in the mid 1990s resulted in its popularization and incorporation into virtually every aspect of modern human life. As of 2009, an estimated quarter of Earth's population used the services of the Internet.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_INTERNETX_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>You get 3 extra [ICON_DIPLOMAT] votes in the world congress.[NEWLINE]  1 [ICON_GREAT_ENGINEER] Great Engineer appears near this City[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness in each City.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_INTERNETX_QUOTE</Tag>
		<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]"During my service in the United States Congress, I took the initiative in creating the Internet." (Al Gore)</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LARGE_HADRON_COLLIDER</Tag>
		<Text>Large Hadron Collider [ICON_RES_MANPOWER]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_LARGE_HADRON_COLLIDER_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>The Large Hadron Collider (LHC) is the world's largest and highest-energy particle accelerator. It is expected that it will address the most fundamental questions of physics, advancing our understanding of the deepest laws of nature.  The LHC lies in a tunnel 27 kilometres (17 mi) in circumference, as much as 175 metres (574 ft) beneath the Franco-Swiss border near Geneva, Switzerland. This synchrotron is designed to collide opposing particle beams of either protons at an energy of 7 teraelectronvolts (1.12 microjoules) per particle, or lead nuclei at an energy of 574 TeV (92.0 µJ) per nucleus.  The term hadron refers to particles composed of quarks.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_LARGE_HADRON_COLLIDER_QUOTE</Tag>
		<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]"If God has created the world, his primary worry was certainly not to make its understanding easy for us" (Albert Einstein)</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HUMAN_BRAIN_MAP</Tag>
		<Text>Human Brain Map [ICON_RES_MANPOWER]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_HUMAN_BRAIN_MAP_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>All neuroimaging can be considered part of brain mapping. Brain mapping can be conceived as a higher form of neuroimaging, producing brain images supplemented by the result of additional (imaging or non-imaging) data processing or analysis, such as maps projecting (measures of) behaviour onto brain regions (see fMRI).  Brain Mapping techniques are constantly evolving, and rely on the development and refinement of image acquisition, representation, analysis, visualization and interpretation techniques. Functional and structural neuroimaging are at the core of the mapping aspect of Brain Mapping.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_HUMAN_BRAIN_MAP_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>+2 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science for every [ICON_CITIZEN] specialist in your empire.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_HUMAN_BRAIN_MAP_QUOTE</Tag>
		<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The worm's brain contains 302 neurons, but the mapping effort took more than a decade. The human brain has an estimated 100 billion neurons and 100 trillion synapses.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FACEBOOK</Tag>
		<Text>Facebook [ICON_RES_MANPOWER]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_FACEBOOK_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>Facebook is a social network service and website launched in February 2004 that is operated and privately owned by Facebook, Inc. As of January 2011, Facebook has more than 600 million active users. Users may create a personal profile, add other users as friends and exchange messages, including automatic notifications when they update their profile. Additionally, users may join common interest user groups, organized by workplace, school, or college, or other characteristics. The name of the service stems from the colloquial name for the book given to students at the start of the academic year by university administrations in the US with the intention of helping students to get to know each other better. Facebook allows anyone who declares themselves to be at least 13 years old to become a registered user of the website.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_FACEBOOK_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>You get 1 extra [ICON_DIPLOMAT] votes in the world congress.[NEWLINE]+20% [ICON_CULTURE] Culture generation Empire wide.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]-25% [ICON_HAPPINESS_4] Unhappiness from number of cities.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_FACEBOOK_QUOTE</Tag>
		<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]"By giving people the power to share, we're making the world more transparent." (Mark Zuckerberg)</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BODY_EXCHANGE</Tag>
		<Text>Body Exchange [ICON_SILVER_FIST][ICON_HEALTH]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BODY_EXCHANGE_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>Doctors can now heal sick patients by replacing entire organs with those grown from organ cultures using the patients own genetic material.  Organ culture is a development from tissue culture methods of research, the organ culture is able to accurately model functions of an organ in various states and conditions by the use of the actual in vitro organ itself.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BODY_EXCHANGE_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>+8 [ICON_GOLD] Gold for every 1 [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizens in this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]10% of [ICON_FOOD] Food is carried over after a new [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizen is born.[NEWLINE]Provides +8 [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower.[NEWLINE]+2 [ICON_HEALTH] Health.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_OPTICAL_INTERCONNECTS</Tag>
		<Text>Optical Interconnects</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_OPTICAL_INTERCONNECTS_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>With the advent of Optical Computing, there is no longer a need for electric to photonic conversions of data.  Optical Interconnects completes the conversion to optical computing by making all points of contact between computers, users, and servers optical, thus greatly increasing network efficiency and lowering costs.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GRID_ENERGY_STORAGE</Tag>
		<Text>Grid Energy Storage</Text>
	</Row>	
	<Row>
		<Tag>KEY_BUILDING_GRID_ENERGY_STORAGE_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>Provides +10 [ICON_POWER3] Electricity.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GRID_ENERGY_STORAGE_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>Grid energy storage (also called large-scale energy storage) refers to the methods used to large-scale store electriCity within an electrical power grid. Electrical energy is stored during times when production (from power plants) exceeds consumption and the stores are utilized at times when consumption exceeds production. In this way, electriCity production need not be drastically scaled up and down to meet momentary consumption – instead, production is maintained at a more constant level. This has the advantage that fuel-based power plants (i.e. coal, oil, gas) can be more efficiently and easily operated at constant production levels.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CLOUD_COMPUTING_NETWORK</Tag>
		<Text>Cloud Computing Network</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CLOUD_COMPUTING_NETWORK_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>Cloud computing is Internet-based computing, whereby shared resources, software, and information are provided to computers and other devices on demand, like the electriCity grid.  Cloud computing users avoid capital expenditure (CapEx) on hardware, software, and services when they pay a provider only for what they use. Consumption is usually billed on a utility (resources consumed, like electriCity) or subscription (time-based, like a newspaper) basis with little or no upfront cost. Other benefits of this approach are low barriers to entry, shared infrastructure and costs, low management overhead, and immediate access to a broad range of applications. In general, users can terminate the contract at any time (thereby avoiding return on investment risk and uncertainty), and the services are often covered by service level agreements (SLAs) with financial penalties.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ADVANCED_SHIPYARD</Tag>
		<Text>Advanced Shipyard</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ADVANCED_SHIPYARD_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>Shipyards and dockyards are places which repair and build ships. These can be yachts, military vessels, cruise liners or other cargo or passenger ships. Dockyards are sometimes more associated with maintenance and basing activities than shipyards, which are sometimes associated more with initial construction. The terms are routinely used interchangeably, in part because the evolution of dockyards and shipyards has often caused them to change or merge roles.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ADVANCED_SHIPYARD_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<Text>Required for CGX Cruiser, Fusion Supercarrier, and Stealth Submarine production.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Requires 2 [ICON_RES_ALUMINUM] Aluminum.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must be built on the coast.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LASER_PERIMETER_DEFENSE</Tag>
		<Text>Laser Perimeter Defense</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LASER_PERIMETER_DEFENSE_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>The laser perimeter defense takes advances used in tactical laser air defense systems, and scales them up for the purpose of City wide air and missile defense.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FUSION_POWER_PLANT</Tag>
		<Text>Fusion Power Plant [ICON_RES_MANPOWER]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_FUSION_POWER_PLANT_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>Fusion power is the power generated by nuclear fusion reactions. In this kind of reaction, two light atomic nuclei fuse together to form a heavier nucleus and in doing so, release a large amount of energy. In a more general sense, the term can also refer to the production of net usable power from a fusion source, similar to the usage of the term "steam power." Most design studies for fusion power plants involve using the fusion reactions to create heat, which is then used to operate a steam turbine, which drives generators to produce electriCity. Except for the use of a thermonuclear heat source, this is similar to most coal, oil, and gas-fired power stations as well as fission-driven nuclear power stations.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_FUSION_POWER_PLANT_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>+20 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production for every 1 [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizens in this City.[NEWLINE]Provides +30 [ICON_POWER3] Electricity[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]You may build up to 1. </Text>
	</Row>
	
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ADVANCED_AUTO_PLANT</Tag>
		<Text>Advanced Auto Plant</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ADVANCED_AUTO_PLANT_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>Auto plants are a type of factory whose sole purpose is to manufacture and assemble automotives.  While a laborous process at first, the invention of the Assembly Line revolutioned the auto industry, as well as the rest of the manufacturing world, by cutting assembly time and costs down to a mere fraction.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ADVANCED_AUTO_PLANT_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<Text>+7 [ICON_GOLD] Gold for every 1 [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizens in this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Required for Gauss Tank and Mass Driver Artillery production.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Requires 2 [ICON_RES_ALUMINUM] Aluminum.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ROBOTIC_OPERATING_ROOM</Tag>
		<Text>Robotic Operating Room [ICON_SILVER_FIST][ICON_HEALTH]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ROBOTIC_OPERATING_ROOM_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>The robotic operating room is a major advance in medical technology.  Allowing doctors to have many precise, powerful tools at their disposal to make surgery quicker, safer, and less invasive than ever before.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ROBOTIC_OPERATING_ROOM_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>+4 [ICON_GOLD] Gold for every 1 [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizen in this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]10% of [ICON_FOOD] Food is carried over after a new [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizen is born.[NEWLINE]Provides +10 [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower.[NEWLINE]+2 [ICON_HEALTH].</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_DINOSAUR_PARK</Tag>
		<Text>Dinosaur Park [ICON_RES_MANPOWER]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_DINOSAUR_PARK_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>The Dinosaur Park is the culmination of years of work, combined Cloning and Genetic Synthesis to take shattered Dinosaur DNA samples, piece them back together, and then clone baby dinosaurs.  Tourists flock to this world wonder, where scientists display and test upon never before seen creatures.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_DINOSAUR_PARK_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>+20 [ICON_GOLD] Gold for every 1 [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizen in this City.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_DINOSAUR_PARK_QUOTE</Tag>
		<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]"Dinosaur fossils? God put those there to test our faith."  Does that trouble anyone here? The idea that God.. might be...fuckin' with our heads? I have trouble sleeping with that knowledge. Some prankster God running around: "Hu hu ho. We will see who believes in me now, ha HA." (Bill Hicks)</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_QUANTUM_SUPERCOMPUTER</Tag>
		<Text>Quantum Supercomputer [ICON_RES_MANPOWER]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_QUANTUM_SUPERCOMPUTER_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>Quantum Supercomputers effectively eclipse their slower ancestors in total computational power.  While the type of computation they perform is different, their extreme scalability allows them to use special emulation software to accomplish any normal task a classical computer could perform in a fraction of the time.  A quantum computer is a device for computation that makes direct use of quantum mechanical phenomena, such as superposition and entanglement, to perform operations on data. Quantum computers are different from traditional computers based on transistors. The basic principle behind quantum computation is that quantum properties can be used to represent data and perform operations on these data.  A theoretical model is the quantum Turing machine, also known as the universal quantum computer.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_QUANTUM_SUPERCOMPUTER_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>You may build up to 1.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_QUANTUM_SUPERCOMPUTER_QUOTE</Tag>
		<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]"2055 – $1,000 computer will match the processing power of all human brains on Earth" (Ray Kurzweil)</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CYBER_COMMAND</Tag>
		<Text>Cyber Command [ICON_RES_MANPOWER]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_CYBER_COMMAND_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>The Cyber Command represents the organization of all defensive duties relating and pertaining to defense networks and computer systems.  In an age of increasing cyber threats, the Cyber Command is a key asset to national defense.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_CYBER_COMMAND_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>+50% Defense from all defensive buildings empire wide.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_CYBER_COMMAND_QUOTE</Tag>
		<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]"USCYBERCOM plans, coordinates, integrates, synchronizes and conducts activities to: direct the operations and defense of specified Department of Defense information networks and; prepare to, and when directed, conduct full spectrum military cyberspace operations in order to enable actions in all domains, ensure US/Allied freedom of action in cyberspace and deny the same to our adversaries." (USCYBERCOM Mission Statement)</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BIO_MEMORY_IMPLANT</Tag>
		<Text>Bio Memory Implant</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BIO_MEMORY_IMPLANT_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>Genetic engineering and organ growth on demand has led to the creation of implantable biological memory augmentations.  Average people can now attain memory speed and accuracy that only supercomputers had access to only a decade before.  The implant also provides access to the cloud which can now perform calculations for the user based upon simple thought queries.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BIO_MEMORY_IMPLANT_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>+10 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science for every 1 [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizen in this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+20 [ICON_GOLD] Gold for every 1 [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizen in this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+20 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production for every 1 [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizen in this City.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LASER_MANUFACTURING_MODULE</Tag>
		<Text>Laser Manufacturing Module</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LASER_MANUFACTURING_MODULE_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>The Laser Manufacturing Module represents the industrialization of high precision laser 3D printing.  Using lasers, base materials are ushered and fused into precise position molecules at a time.  Materials can now be processed and formed at a high quality level down to the nanoscale.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MECHA_PLANT</Tag>
		<Text>Mecha Plant</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MECHA_PLANT_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>Mecha plants are a type of factory whose sole purpose is to manufacture and assemble Mechas.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MECHA_PLANT_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<Text>Required for War Walker production.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Requires 2 [ICON_RES_URANIUM] Uranium.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AI_CORE</Tag>
		<Text>AI Core [ICON_RES_MANPOWER]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_AI_CORE_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>AI is a common topic in both science fiction and projections about the future of technology and society. The existence of an artificial intelligence that rivals human intelligence raises difficult ethical issues, and the potential power of the technology inspires both hopes and fears.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_AI_CORE_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>+1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science for every [ICON_CITIZEN] specialist in your empire.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+5 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production for every [ICON_CITIZEN] specialist in your empire.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+5 [ICON_GOLD] Gold for every [ICON_CITIZEN]  specialist in your empire.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]1 Allowed Per Civ.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_AI_CORE_QUOTE</Tag>
		<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]"2099 – $1,000 computer will match the processing power of 1 Trillion human brains." (Ray Kurzweil)</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_3_LAWS</Tag>
		<Text>3 Laws of Robotics  [ICON_RES_MANPOWER]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_3_LAWS_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>The Three Laws of Robotics, often shortened to The Three Laws or Three Laws, are a set of three rules written by science fiction author Isaac Asimov and later expanded upon. These rules are built in to almost all positronic robots appearing in his fiction and cannot be bypassed. The rules are introduced in his 1942 short story Runaround although they were foreshadowed in a few earlier stories.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_3_LAWS_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>+5 [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness in each City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]1 Allowed Per Civ.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_3_LAWS_QUOTE</Tag>
		<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]1. A robot may not injure a human being or, through inaction, allow a human being to come to harm.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]2. A robot must obey any orders given to it by human beings, except where such orders would conflict with the First Law.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]3. A robot must protect its own existence as long as such protection does not conflict with the First or Second Law.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE] (Isaac Asimov)</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_M_THEORY</Tag>
		<Text>M Theory [ICON_RES_MANPOWER]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_M_THEORY_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>In theoretical physics, M-theory is an extension of string theory in which 11 dimensions are identified. Because the dimensionality exceeds the dimensionality of superstring theories in 10 dimensions, it is believed that the 11-dimensional theory unites all five string theories (and supersedes them). Though a full description of the theory is not yet known, the low-entropy dynamics are known to be supergravity interacting with 2- and 5-dimensional membranes.  This idea is the unique supersymmetric theory in eleven dimensions, with its low-entropy matter content and interactions fully determined, and can be obtained as the strong coupling limit of type IIA string theory because a new dimension of space emerges as the coupling constant increases.  Drawing on the work of a number of string theorists (including Ashoke Sen, Chris Hull, Paul Townsend, Michael Duff and John Schwarz), Edward Witten of the Institute for Advanced Study suggested its existence at a conference at USC in 1995, and used M-theory to explain a number of previously observed dualities, sparking a flurry of new research in string theory called the second superstring revolution.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_M_THEORY_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>+1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science for every [ICON_CITIZEN] specialist in your empire.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]1 Great Scientist appears near this City.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_M_THEORY_QUOTE</Tag>
		<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]"In the history of our intellectual development this will represent the crowning achievement of 2,000 years of investigation into the nature of matter -- space and time." (Michio Kaku)</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_IMMUNITY_CHIP</Tag>
		<Text>Immunity Chip [ICON_HEALTH]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_IMMUNITY_CHIP_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>Immunity Chips represent a breakthrough in modern medicine involving the use of biological nanites, which are extremely tiny machines, to spread throughout the human body fighting disease alongside the natural T-Cells.  These nanites will fight everything from the common cold, to cancer, to rare viruses.  Mortality rates are sharpy reduced and mankind is happier as a result.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_IMMUNITY_CHIP_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>10% of [ICON_FOOD] Food is carried over after a new [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizen is born.[NEWLINE]Increase [ICON_HEALTH] Health by +2.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VR_INTERFACE</Tag>
		<Text>VR Interface</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VR_INTERFACE_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>The VR Interface is the culmination of decades of computer and biological advancement.  Combining the BioComputer Interface with the most advanced simulated environments allows the user the feel like he or she is actually there.  While critics decry this advancement as the beginning of the end of civalization, the value added in happy citzens is clearly in this technology's favor.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_IMAGINARIUM</Tag>
		<Text>Imaginarium [ICON_RES_MANPOWER]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_IMAGINARIUM_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>Using the rapidly adopted VR Interfaces, the Imaginarium is every person's greatest fantasy.  Played out right in their brain with as much or as little sensory input as desired, and multiplied by the billions of people who are all able to simultaneously connect to the same fantasy network.  Everything from love dramas, to pornagraphy; extreme sports to medieval warfare with tens of thousands of participants is all available in the most visceral fashion imaginable.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_IMAGINARIUM_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>+15 [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness in each City.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_IMAGINARIUM_QUOTE</Tag>
		<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]"Can you put a price on your dreams?" (Tony)</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VIRTUAL_SECURITIES_EXCHANGE</Tag>
		<Text>Virtual Securities Exchange [ICON_RES_MANPOWER]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_VIRTUAL_SECURITIES_EXCHANGE_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>Another result of the VR Revolution, the Virtual Securities Exchange is a vast forum where an unlimited number of citizens can enter virtually to buy and sell stocks, bonds, commodities, and any other asset that is bought and sold in traditional stock markets.  With a large amount of power taken from middlemen and brokerages, the entire trading system sees a boost in efficiency, as well as popularity.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_VIRTUAL_SECURITIES_EXCHANGE_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>+60% [ICON_GOLD] Gold from [ICON_CONNECTED] Trade Routes.[</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_VIRTUAL_SECURITIES_EXCHANGE_QUOTE</Tag>
		<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]"Can you put a price on your dreams?" (Tony)</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AI_SECURITY_CENTER</Tag>
		<Text>AI Security Center</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AI_SECURITY_CENTER_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>The AI Security Center uses modern advances in Artificial Intelligence to monitor vast numbers of video, audio, and even internet feeds to ensure that the law is upheld, terrorist plots thwarted, and also so that accidents can be prevented.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AI_SECURITY_CENTER_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>+15% [ICON_FOOD] Food.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NANO_FORGE</Tag>
		<Text>Nano Forge [ICON_SILVER_FIST]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
	<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NANO_FORGE_HELP</Tag>
	<Text>Provides +30 [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower.</Text>
</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NANO_FORGE_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>The Nano Forge is to the 22nd Century as the Factory was to the 20th.  The majority of goods will pass through a Nano Forge at some point in their creation.  The Nano Forge uses advanced laser manufacturing technology to individually place each and every atom in the material, allowing for extreme precise construction of both advanced nano materials, as well as conventional materials that also see benefits from precision control.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GIGA_TOWER</Tag>
		<Text>Giga Tower [ICON_RES_MANPOWER]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_GIGA_TOWER_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>Using high strength carbon nanomaterials, it is now possible to build skyscrapers that climb miles into the sky.  The Giga Tower gets it's name from the sheer amount of materials used in it's construction.  Often weighing more than a Billion kilograms, care must be taken in weight distribution so as to minimize stress on fault lines beneath the City.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_GIGA_TOWER_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>+25% [ICON_CULTURE] Culture Empire Wide.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]1 Allowed Per Civ.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_GIGA_TOWER_QUOTE</Tag>
		<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]"Manhattan has no choice but the skyward extrusion of the Grid itself; only the Skyscraper offers business the wide-open spaces of a man-made Wild West, a frontier in the sky." (Rem Koolhaas)</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FORCE_FIELD</Tag>
		<Text>Force Field</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FORCE_FIELD_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>The Force Field uses an application of 2D Energy Fields, and very large amounts of power, to completely envelop a City in a powerful Force Field that aids in it's defense.  The Force Field has the added benefit that it can be turned on to blunt the impact of major meteorological events, reducing the annual cost of weather related repairs in the City.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BEEF_VAT</Tag>
		<Text>Beef Vat</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BEEF_VAT_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>The Beef Vat uses Nanites, Genetic Synthesis, and a fair amount of electricty to grow almost any food item from it's base elements.  While at first rejected by the population due to prejudices against non-natural food, Beef Vat technology has managed to catch on in cities whose enourmous size demands a cheap, unending source of nourishment.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BEEF_VAT_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>+5 [ICON_FOOD] Food for every [ICON_GREAT_MERCHANT] Merchant Specialist in this City.[NEWLINE]-1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production per [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizen.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_IMPLANT_STATION</Tag>
		<Text>Implant Station</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_IMPLANT_STATION_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>Brain implants, often referred to as neural implants, are technological devices that connect directly to a biological subject's brain - usually placed on the surface of the brain, or attached to the brain's cortex. A common purpose of modern brain implants and the focus of much current research is establishing a biomedical prosthesis circumventing areas in the brain that have become dysfunctional after a stroke or other head injuries. This includes sensory substitution, e.g., in vision. Other brain implants are used in animal experiments simply to record brain activity for scientific reasons. Some brain implants involve creating interfaces between neural systems and computer chips. This work is part of a wider research field called brain-computer interfaces.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_IMPLANT_STATION_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>+4 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production for every 1 [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizens in this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+4 [ICON_GOLD] Gold for every 1 [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizens in this City.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BEHAVIORAL_MOD_CHIP</Tag>
		<Text>Behavioral Mod Chip</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BEHAVIORAL_MOD_CHIP_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>Behavioral Modification Chips use technology related to the Bio Memory Implant to tap into certain regions of the brain responsible for criminal agression and mental instability.  The Behavioral Mod Chip is used on Criminals and Mental Patients to regulate unhealthy impulses for a better life and enhanced community interaction.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AI_COURT</Tag>
		<Text>AI Court</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AI_COURT_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>The AI Court is the culmination of thousands of years in judicial advancement.  The AI Court provides a completely impartial viewpoint regarding matters of law, rendering judgements and guiding court proceedings based upon facts without outside influence.  While Juries are still available and widely used, the AI assigned to the case is able to streamline the process and render impartial rulings when needed.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AI_COURT_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>Eliminates extra [ICON_HAPPINESS_4] Unhappiness from an [ICON_OCCUPIED] Occupied City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Replaces the Courthouse.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MOLECULAR_FABRICATION_PLANT</Tag>
		<Text>Molecular Fabrication Plant</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MOLECULAR_FABRICATION_PLANT_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>The Molecular Fabrication Plant is a highly specialized form of nanoforge that is specifically designed to create precision materials for air and spacecraft that is far above the requirements of any other commercial and military needs.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MOLECULAR_FABRICATION_PLANT_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>Required for the construction of the Space Bomber, Space Fighter, Hunter Killer, and Orbital Strike Missile.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Requires 2 [ICON_RES_COAL] Coal.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BEAM_FOUNDRY</Tag>
		<Text>Beam Foundry</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BEAM_FOUNDRY_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>The Beam Foundry is a special fabrication plant that deals with cutting edge Particle Beam Weaponry.  Fabrication of these weapons requires a specialized containment chamber designed to handle the extreme radiation produced during the production and testing of these weapons.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BEAM_FOUNDRY_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>Requires 2 [ICON_RES_COAL] Coal.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MIND_CONTROL_NETWORK</Tag>
		<Text>Mind Control Network</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MIND_CONTROL_NETWORK_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>The Mind Control Network is a system of neural stimulations that are broadcast through the air, internet, and other means to make the citizens feel more content with their circumstances in life.  While direct though control could also be had of weaker willed citizens, most governments find that simply guiding citizens thought's to a more positive outlook is the best application of this technology.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MIND_CONTROL_NETWORK_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>-5 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production for every 1 [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizens in this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]-5 [ICON_GOLD] Gold for every 1 [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizens in this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]-1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science for every 1 [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizens in this City.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SPACE_ELEVATOR</Tag>
		<Text>Space Elevator [ICON_RES_MANPOWER]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_SPACE_ELEVATOR_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>With the mass production of Carbon Nano Materials, space elevators are finally feasible.  A space elevator is a proposed non-rocket spacelaunch structure (a structure designed to transport material from a celestial body's surface into space). Many elevator variants have been suggested, all of which involve travelling along a fixed structure instead of using rocket powered space launch. The concept most often refers to a cable that reaches from the surface of the Earth on or near the Equator to geostationary orbit (GSO) at 26,199 miles above the earth's surface, and a counter-mass somewhere beyond that point.  The concept of a space elevator dates back to 1895 when Konstantin Tsiolkovsky proposed a free-standing "Tsiolkovsky" tower reaching from the surface of Earth to geostationary orbit. Most recent discussions focus on tensile structures (specifically, tethers) reaching from geostationary orbit to the ground. This structure would be held in tension between Earth and the counterweight in space like a guitar string held taut. Space elevators have also sometimes been referred to as beanstalks, space bridges, space lifts, space ladders, skyhooks, orbital towers, or orbital elevators.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_SPACE_ELEVATOR_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>Greatly increases [ICON_GOLD] Gold,  [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, and [ICON_RESEARCH] Science in the City where this is built.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+30% [ICON_CULTURE] Culture Empire Wide.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]1 Allowed Per Civ.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_SPACE_ELEVATOR_QUOTE</Tag>
		<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]"The space elevator will be built about 50 years after everyone stops laughing." (Arthur C. Clarke)</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ARCOLOGY</Tag>
		<Text>Arcology</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ARCOLOGY_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>The Arcology is the pinnacle of human urban development.  These towering colossi of Carbon and other nano materials span miles in width and often reach a mile into the sky, sheltering millions of people from the elements and gathering them into central locations where they do business with countless residents.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ARCOLOGY_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>+40 [ICON_GOLD] Gold for every 1 [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizens in this City.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VACUUM_DRYDOCK</Tag>
		<Text>Vacuum Drydock</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VACUUM_DRYDOCK_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>The Vacuum Drydock is the shipbuilding industry's answer to the NanoTech Revolution.  These enourmous vacuum chambers enable the same precision found in the production of small items like Consumer Goods and Aircraft, to be had in the construction of the gargantuan ships that the navy employs.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_VACUUM_DRYDOCK_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>Required for the construction of the Submersible Carrier, Fusion Dreadnaught, Supercaviating Submarine, and Plasma Destoyer.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Requires 2 [ICON_RES_COAL] Coal.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must be built on the coast.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SPACE_MANIPULATION_TESTING_STATION</Tag>
		<Text>Space Manipulation Testing Station [ICON_RES_MANPOWER]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_SPACE_MANIPULATION_TESTING_STATION_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>The Space Manipulation Testing Station is an orbital research facility that is being used to test applications of Warp Theory.  Due to the potentially catastrophic nature of these tests, they are conducted at an orbit that halfway to the moon, which is much greater than most stations and satelites.  The research station hopes to achieve advances that may one day lead to anti-gravity, warp drive, and a host of other sought after capabilities.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_SPACE_MANIPULATION_TESTING_STATION_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>1 Allowed Per Civ.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_SPACE_MANIPULATION_TESTING_STATION_QUOTE</Tag>
		<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]"Nothing puzzles me more than time and space; and yet nothing troubles me less" (Charles Lamb)</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_EMPATHIC_NETWORK</Tag>
		<Text>Empathic Network [ICON_RES_MANPOWER]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_EMPATHIC_NETWORK_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>The Empathic Network represents further development into VR and mind-to-mind communications.  Allowing humans to share thoughts and emotions almost instantly and completely, the network allows greater efficiency in all aspects of the economy and brings society to even greater heights of connectedness.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_EMPATHIC_NETWORK_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>+2 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science for every [ICON_CITIZEN] specialist in your empire.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+10 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production for every specialist in your empire.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+10 [ICON_GOLD] Gold for every specialist in your empire.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]1 Allowed Per Civ.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_EMPATHIC_NETWORK_QUOTE</Tag>
		<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]"That is the exploration that awaits you! Not mapping stars and studying nebula, but charting the unknown possibilities of existence" (Leonard Nimoy)</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ROBOT_DISTRICT</Tag>
		<Text>Robot District</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ROBOT_DISTRICT_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>The Robot District is a place where Sentient Robots can go to live with and among themselves.  While many proponents of the district point to it's ability to give Robots a place to call their own, most people also realize that many humans are not ready to accept robots as equals, let alone neighbors.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ROBOTIC_EGALITARIAN_ACT</Tag>
		<Text>Robotic Egalitarian Act [ICON_RES_MANPOWER]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_ROBOTIC_EGALITARIAN_ACT_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>The Robotic Egalitarian Act is a recognition of machine sentience, and as such sentient beings, deserve certain rights as well as respect.  Many of course see it as a self serving attempt to appease Robots so that they do not feel oppressed or threatened by humanity.  While that is likely true, most agree that given the extreme interdependence of humans and machines, that both sides would be better off if they got along.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_ROBOTIC_EGALITARIAN_ACT_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production for every [ICON_CITIZEN] specialist in your empire.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+5 [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness per City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]1 Allowed Per Civ.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_ROBOTIC_EGALITARIAN_ACT_QUOTE</Tag>
		<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]"They hate us, you know... The humans." (Gigolo Joe)  </Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_OCEAN_HABITAT_PROTOTYPE</Tag>
		<Text>Ocean Habitat Prototype</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_OCEAN_HABITAT_PROTOTYPE_DESC</Tag>
		<Text>The Ocean Habitat Prototype is the beginning stage of a push to colonize the oceans.  Given the prevalence of nanotechnology and energyfields, politicians and engineers feel it is finally time to tap the vast potential that the ocean presents to humanity.  Environmental groups strongly disagree.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_OCEAN_HABITAT_PROTOTYPE_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>+4 [ICON_GOLD] Gold from Water Tiles.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+20 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production from Water Tiles.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+4 [ICON_FOOD] Food from Water Tiles.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must be built on the coast.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]1 Allowed Per Civ.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_WONDER_OCEAN_HABITAT_PROTOTYPE_QUOTE</Tag>
		<Text>[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]"But more wonderful than the lore of old men and the lore of books is the secret lore of ocean." (H. P. Lovecraft)</Text>
	</Row>

	<Update>
		<Set Text="Greatly increases [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness in the empire."/>
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_FORBIDDEN_PALACE_HELP" />
	</Update>	
	<Update>
		<Set Text="City must be built on or next to Desert.[NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_FOOD] Food, +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, and +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold for all desert tiles worked by this city (except Flood Plains)."/>
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_PETRA_HELP" />
	</Update>	
	<Update>
		<Set Text="Petra [ICON_RES_MANPOWER]" />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PETRA" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="1 Free [ICON_CULTURE] Social Policy.[NEWLINE]Must be constructed in a coastal city."/>
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_SYDNEY_OPERA_HOUSE_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
	<Set Text="Sydney Opera House [ICON_RES_MANPOWER]" />
	<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SYDNEY_OPERA_HOUSE" />
</Update>
	<!--<Update>
			<Set Text="A Great Artist appears in the City where this building was constructed."/>
			<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_HAGIA_SOPHIA_HELP" />
		</Update>-->	
	<Update>
		<Set Text="Hagia Spohia [ICON_RES_MANPOWER]" />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HAGIA_SOPHIA" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production from [ICON_GREAT_ARTIST] Artist Specialist in every City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Must have built a Monument in all Cities. The cost goes up the more cities there are in the empire."/>
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NATIONAL_EPIC_HELP" />
	</Update>	
	<Update>
		<Set Text="National Epic [ICON_RES_MANPOWER]" />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NATIONAL_EPIC" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="+1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold from [ICON_GREAT_ARTIST] Artist Specialist in every City."/>
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_SISTINE_CHAPEL_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
	<Set Text="Sistine Chapel [ICON_RES_MANPOWER]" />
	<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SISTINE_CHAPEL" />
</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="+1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science from [ICON_GREAT_SCIENTIST] Scientist Specialist in every City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]1 Free Technology.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Must have built a University in all Cities.[INEWLINE]The cost goes up the more cities there are in the empire."/>
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_OXFORD_UNIVERSITY_HELP" />
	</Update>	
	<Update>
		<Set Text="Oxfort University [ICON_RES_MANPOWER]" />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_OXFORD_UNIVERSITY" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="City must be built next to a River or Lake."/>
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GARDEN_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="Greatly increases [ICON_CULTURE] Culture in this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have a Museum."/>
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BROADCAST_TOWER_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="City must have a Bank."/>
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_STOCK_EXCHANGE_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="City must have a Market."/>
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BANK_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="Each source of [ICON_RES_IRON] Iron worked by this City produces +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have a Military Academy."/>
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ARSENAL_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="Provides +1 [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness for every 2 [ICON_CULTURE] Social Policies you have adopted."/>
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_EIFFEL_TOWER_HELP" />
	</Update>	
	<Update>
		<Set Text="Eifel Tower [ICON_RES_MANPOWER]" />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_EIFFEL_TOWER" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="+1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold from [ICON_GREAT_MERCHANT] Merchant Specialist in every City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must be built within 2 tiles of a Mountain that is inside your territory."/>
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_MACHU_PICHU_HELP" />
	</Update>	
	<Update>
		<Set Text="Machu Pichu [ICON_RES_MANPOWER]" />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MACHU_PICHU" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="Each source of [ICON_RES_IRON] Iron or [ICON_RES_COPPER] Copper worked by this City produces +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have a mined source of [ICON_RES_IRON] Iron or [ICON_RES_COPPER] Copper nearby.[NEWLINE]Provides +2 [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower."/>
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FORGE_HELP" />
	</Update>	
	<Update>
		<Set Text="Forge [ICON_SILVER_FIST]" />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FORGE" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="10% of [ICON_FOOD] Food is carried over after a new [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizen is born.[NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold in every tile next to a River.[NEWLINE]Provides +1 [ICON_RES_MANPOWER].[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must be built next to a River.[NEWLINE]City must have a Sewer System."/>
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AQUEDUCT_HELP" />
	</Update>	
	<Update>
		<Set Text="Aqueduct [ICON_SILVER_FIST]" />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AQUEDUCT" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="+2 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture per turn from [ICON_RES_INCENSE] Incense and +2 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture from [ICON_RES_WINE] Grapes nearby.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have an improved source of at least one of these resources nearby." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MONASTERY_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="+1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science for every 2 [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizens in this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Must have built a Library in all Cities. The cost goes up the more cities there are in the empire." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NATIONAL_COLLEGE_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="10% [ICON_FOOD] Food is saved when a new [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizen is born.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]+2 [ICON_PEACE] Faith, +2 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and +5 [ICON_FOOD] Food ." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_TEMPLE_ARTEMIS_HELP" />
	</Update>	
	<Update>
		<Set Text="Temple of Artemis [ICON_RES_MANPOWER][ICON_HEALTH]" />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TEMPLE_ARTEMIS" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production in every tile next to a River.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Requires 1 [ICON_RES_ALUMINUM] Aluminum for Construction.[NEWLINE]City must be built next to a River." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HYDRO_PLANT_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="+2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold from water tiles worked by this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must be built on the coast." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_COLOSSUS_HELP" />
	</Update>	
	<Update>
		<Set Text="Colossus [ICON_RES_MANPOWER]" />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_COLOSSUS" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production from Engineer Specialists in every City.[NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold from Merchant Specialists in every City.[NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science from Scientist Specialist and Artist Specialist in every City." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_STATUE_OF_LIBERTY_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
	<Set Text="Statue of Liberty [ICON_RES_MANPOWER]" />
	<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_STATUE_OF_LIBERTY" />
</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="Add yields +2 [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age Points.[NEWLINE]Provides 3 [ICON_MISSIONARY] Missionaries.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Can only be build in a Holy City." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LIBRARY_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
	<Set Text="+1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science for every 2 [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizens in this City." />
	<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BOROBUDUR" />
</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="+1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science for every 2 [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizens in this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have a University." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PUBLIC_SCHOOL_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="City must have a Public School." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LABORATORY_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="+2 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science from Jungle tiles worked by this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have a Library." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_UNIVERSITY_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="Significantly increases [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production in this City.[NEWLINE]Provides 4 [ICON_POWER3] Electricity.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Requires a nearby desert for construction.[NEWLINE]City must have a Factory." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SOLAR_PLANT_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="Requires 1 [ICON_POWER3] Electricity for construction." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FACTORY_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="Cities constructed on hills may not build Windmills.[NEWLINE]Provides +2 [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WINDMILL_HELP" />
	</Update>	
	<Update>
		<Set Text="Windmill [ICON_SILVERFIST][ICON_HEALTH]" />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WINDMILL" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="+1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold from [ICON_GREAT_MERCHANT] Merchant Specialists in every City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Requires Markets in every City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Cost increases for each additional City." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NATIONAL_TREASURY_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="+1 [ICON_FOOD] Food from Water Tiles. +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food from Sea Resources worked by this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must be built on the coast." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LIGHTHOUSE_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<!--<Update>
			<Set Text="+15 XP for Naval Units produced in this City. Forms a [ICON_CONNECTED] Trade Route with the [ICON_CAPITAL] Capital over water (if they're not already [ICON_CONNECTED] connected by land).[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must be built on the coast." />
			<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HARBOR_HELP" />
		</Update>-->
	<Update>
		<Set Text="+1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold from Water Tiles.[NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production from Sea Resources worked by this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have a Harbor." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SEAPORT_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="City must be built next to a River.[NEWLINE]Provides +1 [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WATERMILL_HELP" />
	</Update>	
	<Update>
		<Set Text="Watermill [ICON_SILVER_FIST]" />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WATERMILL" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="Required for Supercarrier, A-Bomb, Nuclear Missile, and Nuclear Submarine production. Provides 14 [ICON_POWER3] Electricity [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have a Factory. Requires 2 [ICON_RES_URANIUM] Uranium." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NUCLEAR_PLANT_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="City must be built within 2 tiles of a Mountain." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_OBSERVATORY_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="10% of [ICON_FOOD] Food is carried over after a new [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizen is born." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HOSPITAL_STRATEGY" />
	</Update>	
	<Update>
		<Set Text="Hospital [ICON_HEALTH]" />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HOSPITAL" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="Each source of [ICON_RES_URANIUM] Uranium worked by this City produces +3 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have a Hospital." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MEDICAL_LAB_HELP" />
	</Update>	
	<Update>
		<Set Text="Medical Lab [ICON_HEALTH]" />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MEDICAL_LAB" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="All newly-trained Units in this City receive the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Morale[ENDCOLOR] Promotion, improving [ICON_STRENGTH] combat strength by 15%.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Must have built a Barracks in all Cities.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE] May build up to 1." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HEROIC_EPIC_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="Must have built a Workshop in all Cities.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]May build up to 1." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_IRONWORKS_HELP" />
	</Update>



	<!-- TODO: Insert table data example here.-->

	<!-- Buildings-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SCHOKOLADE">
		<Text>Choclate Shop</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SCHOKOLADE_HELP">
		<Text>Provides two resources of [ICON_RES_CHOCLATE] Choclate.[NEWLINE]Add yields +4 [ICON_GOLD] Gold and [ICON_FOOD] Food to every worked source of [ICON_RES_CACAO] Cacao.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Requires[ENDCOLOR] 5 [ICON_RES_CACAO] Cacao to be build.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SCHOKOLADE_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Provides two extra luxus Resources of [ICON_RES_CHOCLATE] Choclate.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_SCHOKOLADE_TEXT">
		<Text>A Choclate Shop is a dedicated building for the making of choclate.</Text>
	</Row>

	<!--OLIVES-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_OLIVES">
		<Text>Olives</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_OLIVES_HELP">
		<Text>+2 [ICON_FOOD] Food when improved by a Plantation. Only found in dry regions.[NEWLINE]Provides [ICON_RES_OLIVE_OIL] Olive Oil if the City has built an [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Olive Press[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_RESOURCE_OLIVES">
		<Text>Olives</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_RESOURCE_OLIVES_TEXT">
		<Text>Olive cultivation is centered on the coastal areas of the Mediterranean Sea, and provides over 90% of the olives for World markets. An ancient crop, olives were first cultivated by the Greeks, but the Romans spread their cultivation throughout their empire.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_OLIVE_OIL">
		<Text>Olive Oil</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_OLIVE_OIL_HELP">
		<Text>Produced at the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Olive Press[ENDCOLOR] Building.[NEWLINE]+3 [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_RESOURCE_OLIVE_OIL">
		<Text>Olive Oil</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_RESOURCE_OLIVE_OIL_TEXT">
		<Text>Olive oil is a fat obtained from the olive (the fruit of Olea europaea; family Oleaceae), a traditional tree crop of the Mediterranean Basin. The oil is produced by grinding whole olives and extracting the oil by mechanical or chemical means. It is commonly used in cooking, cosmetics, pharmaceuticals, and soaps and as a fuel for traditional oil lamps. Olive oil is used throughout the world, but especially in the Mediterranean countries.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_OLIVE_PRESS">
		<Text>Olive Press</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_OLIVE_PRESS_HELP">
		<Text>Produces 2 [ICON_RES_OLIVE_OIL] Olive Oil, increasing [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness. +1[ICON_GOLD] Gold on [ICON_RES_OLIVES] Olives.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Requires a nearby source of [ICON_RES_OLIVES] Olives.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_OLIVE_PRESS_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Build an Olive Press in cities near Olive resources. Trade the surplus Olive Oil the building produces to other Civilizations.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_OLIVE_PRESS_TEXT">
		<Text>People have used olive presses since Greeks first began making olive oil over 5000 years ago. Extant Roman era olive presses survive to the present time, with a notable collection present at Volubilis in Morocco.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]An olive press works by applying pressure to olive paste to separate the liquid oil and vegetation water from the solid material. The oil and vegetation water are then separated by standard decantation.</Text>
	</Row>

	<!--Platinum-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_PLATINUM">
		<Text>Platinum</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_PLATINUM_HELP">
		<Text>+4 [ICON_GOLD] Gold if the nearby City has a [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Stock Exchange[ENDCOLOR].[NEWLINE]Provides [ICON_RES_JEWELRY] Jewelry if the City has built a [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Jeweler[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_RESOURCE_PLATINUM">
		<Text>Platinum</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_RESOURCE_PLATINUM_TEXT">
		<Text>Platinum is a scarce precious metal, and is used in both industrial and luxury good production. It is often traded as an expensive commodity.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Update>
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_STOCK_EXCHANGE_HELP" />
		<Set Text="City must have a Bank. Nearby [ICON_RES_PLATINUM] Platinum resources produce +5 [ICON_GOLD] Gold." />
	</Update>

	<!--Schreinerei-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SCHREINER">
		<Text>Cabinetmaker</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SCHREINER_HELP">
		<Text>Provides one resources of [ICON_RES_FURNITURE] Furniture.[NEWLINE]Add yields +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold and [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, to each worked source of wood.[NEWLINE]Needs three Resources of[ICON_RES_WOOD] Wood and the building Lumberjack must build in the City.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SCHREINER_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Provides one extra luxus Resources of Furniture.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_SCHREINER_TEXT">
		<Text>A Cabinetmaker is a dedicated building for the making of Furniture.</Text>
	</Row>

	<!--Geothermal Power Plant-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GEOTHERM">
		<Text>Geothermal Power Plant</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GEOTHERM_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Provides [ICON_POWER3] Electricity and a [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production boost.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GEOTHERM_HELP">
		<Text>+9 [ICON_POWER3]Electricity and gives +5 [ICON_PRODUCTION]Production for Mountains worked by this city.[NEWLINE]City must be built near a Mountain and must contain a Factory.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GEOTHERM_PEDIA">
		<Text>In the 20th century, demand for electricity led to the consideration of geothermal power as a generating source.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Prince Piero Ginori Conti tested the first geothermal power generator on 4 July 1904 in Larderello, Italy.</Text>
	</Row>

	<!--Coal Plant-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KOHLEKRAFTWERK">
		<Text>Coal Plant</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KOHLEKRAFTWERK_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Provides [ICON_POWER3] Electricity and a [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production boost.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KOHLEKRAFTWERK_HELP">
		<Text>Provides +8 [ICON_POWER3] Electricity City must not contain a factory.[NEWLINE]Requires 4 [ICON_RES_COAL] Coal.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KOHLEKRAFTWERK_PEDIA">
		<Text>Coal is primarily used as a solid fuel to produce electricity and heat through combustion. World coal consumption was about 6.75 billion short tons in 2006 and is expected to increase 48% to 9.98 billion short tons by 2030.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]China produced 2.38 billion tons in 2006. India produced about 447.3 million tons in 2006. 68.7% of China's electricity comes from coal. The USA consumes about 14% of the world total, using 90% of it for generation of electricity.</Text>
	</Row>

	<!--Solar Tower-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SOLARTOWER">
		<Text>Solar Tower</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SOLARTOWER_HELP">
		<Text>[ICON_RES_URAN] Uran, [ICON_RES_OEL] oel and [ICON_RES_COAL] coal provides +1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science and provides +12 [ICON_POWER3] Electricity.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Requirement[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE]The city must build near a desert.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SOLARTOWER_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Allowes you a [ICON_RESEARCH] science bonus from worked resources of [ICON_RES_URAN] uran, [ICON_RES_COAL] coal and [ICON_RES_OIL] oil and provides +12 [ICON_POWER3] Electricity.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SOLARTOWER_PEDIA">
		<Text>The solar updraft tower (SUT) is a renewable-energy power plant for generating electricity from solar power. Sunshine heats the air beneath a very wide greenhouse-like roofed collector structure surrounding the central base of a very tall chimney tower. The resulting convection causes a hot air updraft in the tower by the chimney effect. This airflow drives wind turbines placed in the chimney updraft or around the chimney base to produce electricity. Plans for scaled-up versions of demonstration models will allow significant power generation, and may allow development of other applications, such as water extraction or distillation, and agriculture or horticulture. As a solar chimney power plant (SCPP) proposal for electrical power generation, commercial investment is discouraged by the high initial cost of building a very large novel structure, and by the risk of investment in a feasible but unproven application of even proven component technology for long-term returns on investment—especially when compared to the proven and demonstrated greater short-term returns on lesser investment in coal-fired or nuclear power plants. Likewise, the benefits of 'clean' or solar power technologies are shared, and the widely shared harmful pollution of existing power generation technologies is not applied as a cost for private commercial investment. This is a well-described economic trade-off between private benefit and shared cost, versus shared benefit and private cost. If it is in the public interest, then some form of public investment or subsidy to share cost and risk will be required to demonstrate SCPP feasibility at scale..</Text>
	</Row>

	<!--Windturbines-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WINDTURBINEN_HELP">
		<Text>+6 [ICON_POWER3] Electricity.[NEWLINE]Needs 4 [ICON_RES_IRON] Iron and a flatland.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WINDTURBINEN">
		<Text>Windturbines</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_WINDTURBINEN_TEXT">
		<Text>Provides 8 [ICON_POWER3] Electricity.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WINDTURBINEN_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Boost to the city [ICON_PRODUCTION] production and provides 8 [ICON_POWER3] Electricity.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WINDTURBINEN_PEDIA">
		<Text>A wind turbine is a device that converts kinetic energy from the wind, also called wind energy, into mechanical energy in a process known as wind power. If the mechanical energy is used to produce electricity, the device may be called a wind turbine or wind power plant. If the mechanical energy is used to drive machinery, such as for grinding grain or pumping water, the device is called a windmill or wind pump. Similarly, it may be referred to as a wind charger when used for charging batteries. The result of over a millennium of windmill development and modern engineering, today's wind turbines are manufactured in a wide range of vertical and horizontal axis types. The smallest turbines are used for applications such as battery charging or auxiliary power on boats; while large grid-connected arrays of turbines are becoming an increasingly important source of wind power-produced commercial electricity.</Text>
	</Row>

	<!--Local Gouverment-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FEUDAL_HELP">
		<Text>1% [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happines in your Civilization and provides a [ICON_STRENGTH] defence bonus in the City it was build.[NEWLINE]Increase [ICON_ORDER] Order by +2.[NEWLINE]Need at least 5 Cities to be build and you may construct up to three.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FEUDAL">
		<Text>Local Gouverment [ICON_ORDER]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_FEUDAL_TEXT">
		<Text>upps</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FEUDAL_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Boost global [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] happiness and gives a local [ICON_STRENGTH] defence bonus.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FEUDAL_PEDIA">
		<Text>upps</Text>
	</Row>

	<!--Lumberjack-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LUMBERJACK">
		<Text>Lumberjack [ICON_SILVER_FIST]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LUMBERJACK_HELP">
		<Text>+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production from forest and jungle tiles.[NEWLINE]Provides +1 [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Requires[ENDCOLOR] a nearby Forest to be build.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LUMBERJACK_PEDIA">
		<Text>A lumberjack is a worker in the logging industry who performs the initial harvesting and transport of trees for ultimate processing into forest products. The term usually refers to a bygone era (before 1945 in the United States) when hand tools were used in harvesting trees. Because of its historical ties, the term lumberjack has become ingrained in popular culture through folklore, mass media and spectator sports. The actual work was difficult, dangerous, intermittent, low-paying, and primitive in living conditions, but the men built a traditional culture that celebrated strength, masculinity, confrontation with danger, and resistance to modernization.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LUMBERJACK_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Use the Lumberjack to boost your cities production, while keeping woods alive.</Text>
	</Row>

	<!--Dungeon-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KERKER">
		<Text>Dungeon [ICON_PLAGUE]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KERKER_PEDIA">
		<Text>A dungeon is a room or cell in which prisoners are held, especially underground.[NEWLINE]Dungeons are generally associated with medieval castles, though their association with torture probably belongs more to the Renaissance period.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]An oubliette is a form of dungeon which is accessible only from a hatch in a high ceiling.The word dungeon comes from Old French donjon (also spelt dongeon), which in its earliest usage meant a keep, the main tower of a castle. The first recorded instance of the word in English near the beginning of the 14th century also meant "an underground prison cell beneath the castle keep". While some sources cite Medieval Latin dom(i)niōn- "property" (and ultimately dominus "lord") as the original source, it is more likely that the word derives from the Frankish *dungjo, *dungjon- ("dungeon, vault, bower"), from Proto-Germanic *dungijōn, *dungō ("an enclosed space, treasury, vault"), from Proto-Indo-European *dʰengʰ- ("to cover, hide, conceal"),[1] related to Old Saxon dung ("underground vault, cellar"), Old High German tung ("a cellar, underground living quarter"), Old English dung ("a dungeon, prison"), and Old Norse dyngja ("a detached apartment, lady's bower"). In English, a dungeon now usually only signifies the sense of underground prison or oubliette, typically in a basement of a castle, whereas the alternate spelling donjon is generally reserved for the original meaning.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KERKER_HELP">
		<Text>Reduce the enemy [ICON_SPY] spyrate and [ICON_CULTURE] cultureinfluence and speed ups your [ICON_WORKER] workers.[NEWLINE]Increase [ICON_PLAGUE] Plague by+1.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KERKER_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Reduced enemy [ICON_CULTURE] Culture by 5%, enemy [ICON_SPY] spyrate in this town by 10% and all [ICON_WORKER] worker are working 1% faster.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Note[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE] City need the building walls.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_KERKER_TEXT">
		<Text>The Dungeon reduce enemy influence in this city and improves the workrate in your Civilisation</Text>
	</Row>

	<!--BERGWERK-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BERGWERK">
		<Text>Pit [ICON_SILVER_FIST]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BERGWERK_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Provides a boost to [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and [ICON_GOLD] Gold.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BERGWERK_HELP">
		<Text>Adds yields +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold and +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production to every Mountain worked by this City. Provides +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold when [NEWLINE][COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Copper Working[ENDCOLOR] is discovered.[NEWLINE]Provides +1 [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Note[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE] City must build near a Mountain. </Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BERGWERK_PEDIA">
		<Text>[NEWLINE]Upps[NEWLINE]</Text>
	</Row>
  <!-- Enter your Game Data here. -->
	<!-- Buildings-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BLACKSMITH_HELP">
		<Text>+3 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production.[NEWLINE]Requires [ICON_RES_IRON] Iron or [ICON_RES_COPPER] Copper.[NEWLINE]Provides +1[ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BLACKSMITH">
		<Text>Blacksmith [ICON_SILVER_FIST]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_BLACKSMITH_TEXT">
		<Text>Blacksmiths produce all manner of metal products.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BLACKSMITH_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Blacksmith, must have iron or copper withing city borders</Text>
	</Row>

	<!--WEAPONSMITH-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WEAPONSMITH_HELP">
		<Text>+15 [ICON_WAR] XP for all land [ICON_SILVER_FIST] units and free Fine Weapon's Promotion.[NEWLINE]Provides +1 [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WEAPONSMITH">
		<Text>Weaponsmith [ICON_SILVER_FIST]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_WEAPONSMITH_TEXT">
		<Text>Weaponsmiths produce fine weapons.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WEAPONSMITH_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Weaponsmith, must have iron withing city borders.</Text>
	</Row>

	<!--ARMOUR_WORKSHOP-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ARMOUR_WORKSHOP_HELP">
		<Text>+15 [ICON_WAR] XP and Infantry Armour Promotion to new Gun [NEWLINE]Units.[NEWLINE]Requires [ICON_RES_IRON]Iron.[NEWLINE]Provides +1 [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ARMOUR_WORKSHOP">
		<Text>Armour Workshop [ICON_SILVER_FIST]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_ARMOUR_WORKSHOP_TEXT">
		<Text>A Armour Workshop produces Light Infantry Armour.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ARMOUR_WORKSHOP_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Armour Workshop, must have iron within city borders.</Text>
	</Row>

	<!--FARRIER_-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FARRIER_HELP">
		<Text>+15 [ICON_WAR] XP and Free Horse Shoes Promotion to new Mounted [ICON_SILVER_FIST] Units.[NEWLINE]Requires [ICON_RES_HORSE] Horses or [ICON_RES_IRON] Iron.[NEWLINE]Provides +1 [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpwer.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FARRIER">
		<Text>Farrier [ICON_SILVER_FIST]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_FARRIER_TEXT">
		<Text>A farrier is a specialist in equine hoof care, including the trimming and balancing of a horse's hoof and the placing of shoes to the horse's foot. A farrier couples a subset of the blacksmith's skills with a subset of veterinary medicine to address the care of the horse's feet.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FARRIER_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Farrier, must have Horse or Iron within city borders</Text>
	</Row>

	<!--ARMOURER-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ARMOURER_HELP">
		<Text>+15 [ICON_WAR] XP to Land [ICON_SILVER_FIST] Units and Free Fine Armour Promotion to new Melee and Mounted Units. Requires Iron.[NEWLINE]Provides +1 [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ARMOURER">
		<Text>Armourer [ICON_SILVER_FIST]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_ARMOURER_TEXT">
		<Text>Armourer [ICON_SILVER_FIST]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ARMOURER_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Armourer, must have iron within city borders.</Text>
	</Row>

	<!--IRONMONGER_-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_IRONMONGER_HELP">
		<Text>+15 [ICON_WAR] XP to Land [ICON_SILVER_FIST] Units and Free Reinforced Armour Promotion to new Melee and Mounted Units. Requires Iron.[NEWLINE]Provides +1 [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_IRONMONGER">
		<Text>Iron Monger</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_IRONMONGER_TEXT">
		<Text>Iron Monger [ICON_SILVER_FIST]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_IRONMONGER_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Iron Monger, must have iron within city borders.</Text>
	</Row>

	<!--LEATHERWORK-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LEATHERWORK_HELP">
		<Text>+15 [ICON_WAR] XP to Land [ICON_SILVER_FIST] Units and Free Hardened Leather Promotion to new Recon, Archer, Melee and Mounted Units.[NEWLINE]Requires [ICON_RES_DEER] Deer or [ICON_RES_COW] Cattle.[NEWLINE]Provides +1 [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LEATHERWORK">
		<Text>Leatherworker</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_LEATHERWORK_TEXT">
		<Text>Leatherworker, must have Deer or Cattle within city borders.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LEATHERWORK_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Leatherworker [ICON_SILVER_FIST]</Text>
	</Row>

	<!--SHIPYARDS-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SHIPYARDS">
		<Text>Shipyards</Text>
		<Plurality>2</Plurality>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SHIPYARDS_HELP">
		<Text>Provides free [ICON_WAR] XP for all new trained naval [ICON_SILVER_FIST] units in this City.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_SHIPYARDS_STATBOX">
		<Text>missing stats</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_SHIPYARDS_TEXT">
		<Text>Shore establishment for building and repairing ships. The shipbuilding facilities of the ancient and medieval worlds reached a culmination in the arsenal of Venice, a shipyard in which a high degree  of organization produced an assembly-line technique, with a ship’s fittings added to the completed hull as it was floated past successive docks. In 18th-century British shipyards, the hull was towed to a floating stage called a sheer hulk, where it received its masts and rigging.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SHIPYARDS_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Shipyards provide experience for Naval Military units constructed in the city. This experience can be used to give the units Promotions, making them more effective in battle.</Text>
	</Row>

	<!--UB-->
	<!-- Venice -->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CCTPVENICE1">
		<Text>Venice UB 1</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CCTPVENICE1_STRATEGY">
		<Text>upps</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CCTPVENICE1_HELP">
		<Text>upps</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CCTPVENICE1_PEDIA">
		<Text>[NEWLINE]Upps[NEWLINE].</Text>
	</Row>

	<!-- Venice -->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CCTPVENICE2">
		<Text>Venice UB 1</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CCTPVENICE2_STRATEGY">
		<Text>+20% [ICON_FOOD] Food is saved when a new [ICON_CITIZEN] Cititen is born.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CCTPVENICE2_HELP">
		<Text>upps</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CCTPVENICE2_PEDIA">
		<Text>[NEWLINE]Upps[NEWLINE].</Text>
	</Row>

	<!-- FAITHBUILDINGS -->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_INQUISATION">
		<Text>Witch trials [ICON_SILVER_FIST][ICON_RELIGION]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_INQUISATION_TEXT">
		<Text>Allows the construction of the Witch Hunter, +5 [ICON_Peace] Faith and  gifts a free [ICON_INQUISITOR] Inquisitor.[NEWLINE]Provides +1 [NEWLINE] Manpower.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_INQUISATION_HELP">
		<Text>+5 [ICON_PEACE] Faith and a free [ICON_INQUISITOR] Inquisitor .</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_INQUISATION_STRATEGY">
		<Text>This belief allows the construction of the building Witch Hunter and its reduce the effects of enemy inquisitors as well.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_INQUISATION_PEDIA">
		<Text>The Inquisition was a group of institutions within the judicial system of the Roman Catholic Church whose aim was to combat heresy. It started in 12th-century France to combat the spread of religious sectarianism, in particular the Cathars and the Waldensians. This Medieval Inquisition persisted into the 14th century, from the 1250s associated with the Dominican Order. In the early 14th century, two other movements attracted the attention of the Inquisition, the Knights Templar and the Beguines. At the end of the Middle Ages, the concept and scope of the Inquisition was significantly expanded, now in the historical context of the turmoils of the Protestant Reformation and the Catholic Counter-Reformation. Its geographic scope was expanded to other European countries, as well as throughout the Spanish and Portuguese empires in the Americas, Asia and Africa. Its focus now came to include the persecution of sorcery (an aspect almost entirely absent from the Medieval Inquisition), making it one of the agents in the Early Modern witch-hunts.</Text>
	</Row>

	<!--Ritual Burial-->
	<Update>
		<Set Text="Provides +1 [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happines for each City with this [ICON_RELIGION] Religion, Ritual Burial faith building"/>
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BELIEF_CEREMONIAL_BURIAL"/>
	</Update>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_BESTATTUNGEN_TEXT">
		<Text>upps</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BESTATTUNGEN">
		<Text>Ritual Burial [ICON_RELIGION]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BESTATTUNGEN_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Provides [ICON_GOLD] Gold each time a [ICON_GREAT_PEOPLE] Great Person is expanded.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BESTATTUNGEN_HELP">
		<Text>+2 [ICON_PEACE] Faith, +1 [ICON_Culture] Culture, and +1 [ICON_HAPPINESS] Happiness. Provides 5 [ICON_Gold] Gold every time a Great Person is expanded.</Text>
	</Row>
	<!--Have a nice day:=)-->	
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_ZIRKURAT_TEXT">
		<Text>Zirkurat [ICON_RELIGION]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ZIRKURAT">
		<Text>Zirkurat</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ZIRKURAT_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Provides a +10% [ICON_CULTURE] Culture bonus in the city it was build.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ZIRKURAT_HELP">
		<Text>+10% [ICON_CULTURE] CULTURE, +1 [ICON_PEACE] Faith and +2[ICON_HAPPINESS] Happiness.</Text>
	</Row>

	<!--Nature Gods-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NATURHEILIGTUM">
		<Text>Nature Gods [ICON_RELIGION]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NATURHEILIGTUM_TEXT">
		<Text>upps</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NATURHEILIGTUM_HELP">
		<Text>+1 [ICON_PEACE] Faith from every Natural Wonder and Mountain worked by this city.[NEWLINE]Allowes construction of the Nature Gods building</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NATURHEILIGTUM_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Boost your Faith from Natural Wonders and Mountains.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NATURHEILIGTUM_PEDIA">
		<Text>In nature worship, a nature deity is a deity in charge of forces of nature such as water deity, vegetation deity, sky deity, solar deity, fire deity or any other naturally occurring phenomena such as death deity or fertility deity. Accepted in panentheism, pantheism, deism, polytheism, animism, totemism, shamanism and paganism the deity embodies natural forces and can have characteristics of the mother goddess, Mother Nature or lord of the animals..</Text>
	</Row>

	

	

	<!--Off-Shore Windpark-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_OSWINDPARK">
		<Text>Off-Shore Windpark</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_OSWINDPARK_HELP">
		<Text>+8 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and +8 [ICON_POWER3] Electricity. Needs 1 Iron and 1 Aluminum to build.[NEWLINE]City must build on the coast.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_OSWINDPARK_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Provides a boost in Electricity.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_OSWINDPARK_TEXT">
		<Text>Offshore wind power refers to the construction of wind farms in bodies of water to generate electricity from wind. Better wind speeds are available offshore compared to on land, so offshore wind power’s contribution in terms of electricity supplied is higher, and NIMBY opposition to construction is usually much weaker. However, offshore wind farms are relatively expensive.</Text>
	</Row>

	<!--WALTOURISMUS-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WALTOURISMUS">
		<Text>Whale Watching</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WALTOURISMUS_HELP">
		<Text>+5 [ICON_GOLD] Gold and +5 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture from every worked source of [ICON_RES_WHALE] Whale. Provides +3 [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism when Flight is discovered.[NEWLINE]City need a worked source of Whale, a Hotel must build in the City and it requires one [ICON_POWER3] Electricity.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WALTOURISMUS_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Provides a boost in Culture, Happiness and with the discovering of Flight a Tourism boost.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WALTOURISMUS_PEDIA">
		<Text>upps</Text>
	</Row>

	<!--RACING_CARNIVAL-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RACING_CARNIVAL">
		<Text>Racing Carneval</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RACING_CARNIVAL_HELP">
		<Text>+1 [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism when Radio is discovered.[NEWLINE]Needs one Resources of [ICON_RES_HORSE] Horse to be build.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RACING_CARNIVAL_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Provides a boost in Culture and Happiness.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RACING_CARNIVAL_PEDIA">
		<Text>upps</Text>
	</Row>

	<!--Chieftain Hut-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HUETTE">
		<Text>Chieftain Hut [ICON_SILVER_FIST]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HUETTE_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Provides two free [ICON_SILVER_FIST] Caveman, +10% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production when building land [ICON_SILVER_FIST] units and +15 [ICON_WAR] XP for all land units.[NEWLINE]Provides +1 [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_HUETTE_TEXT">
		<Text>Provides a military bonus in the early game, also it is required to build later the palace.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HUETTE_PEDIA">
		<Text>Chieftain Hut</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_HUETTE_QUOTE">
		<Text>[NEWLINE]"Innovation distinguishes between a leader and a follower."[NEWLINE] -Steve Jobs</Text>
	</Row>
	
	<!--WACHTURM-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WACHTURM">
		<Text>Watchtower</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WACHTURM_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Military [ICON_SILVER_FIST] units get a +10% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production bonus.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WACHTURM_PEDIA">
		<Text>A watchtower is a type of fortification used in many parts of the world. It differs from a regular tower in that its primary use is military, and from a turret in that it is usually a freestanding structure. Its main purpose is to provide a high, safe place from which a sentinel or guard may observe the surrounding area. In some cases, non-military towers, such as religious pagodas, may also be used as watchtowers. An example of nonmilitary watchtower in history is the one of Jerusalem. Though the Hebrews used it to keep a watch for approaching armies, the religious authorities forbade the taking of weapons up into the tower as this would require bringing weapons through the temple. Rebuilt by King Herod, that watchtower was renamed after Mark Antony, his friend who battled against Gaius Julius Caesar Octavianus (later Augustus) and lost.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WACHTURM_HELP">
		<Text>Increase the military [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production in this by +10%.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Note[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE]City must build on a hill and the city must have a wall.</Text>
	</Row>

	<!--Reprocessing plant-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WIEDERAUFBEREITUNGSANLAGE">
		<Text>Reprocessing plant [ICON_PLAGUE]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WIEDERAUFBEREITUNGSANLAGE_STRATEGY">
		<Text>You can build up to five reprocessing plants.[NEWLINE]Each provides +1 [ICON_URAN] Uran but requires a nuclear plant and +4 [ICON_POWER3] Electricity.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WIEDERAUFBEREITUNGSANLAGE_HELP">
		<Text>+4 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and +6 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Note[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE]Increase [ICON_PLAGUE] Plague by +1.[NEWLINE]Requires a nuclear plant and 4 Electricy to built.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_WIEDERAUFBEREITUNGSANLAGE_TEXT">
		<Text>Nuclear reprocessing technology was developed to chemically separate and recover fissionable plutonium from irradiated nuclear fuel. Reprocessing serves multiple purposes, whose relative importance has changed over time. Originally reprocessing was used solely to extract plutonium for producing nuclear weapons. With the commercialization of nuclear power, the reprocessed plutonium was recycled back into MOX nuclear fuel for thermal reactors. The reprocessed uranium, which constitutes the bulk of the spent fuel material, can in principle also be re-used as fuel, but that is only economic when uranium prices are high. Finally, a breeder reactor is not restricted to using recycled plutonium and uranium. It can employ all the actinides, closing the nuclear fuel cycle and potentially multiplying the energy extracted from natural uranium by about 60 times. Nuclear reprocessing reduces the volume of high-level waste, but by itself does not reduce radioactivity or heat generation and therefore does not eliminate the need for a geological waste repository. Reprocessing has been politically controversial because of the potential to contribute to nuclear proliferation, the potential vulnerability to nuclear terrorism, the political challenges of repository siting (a problem that applies equally to direct disposal of spent fuel), and because of its high cost compared to the once-through fuel cycle.</Text>
	</Row>

	<!--WASTE_PLANT-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WASTE_PLANT">
		<Text>Waste Plant [ICON_PLAGUE]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WASTE_PLANT_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Provides [ICON_POWER3] Electricity and a [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production boost.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WASTE_PLANT_HELP">
		<Text>Provides +8 [ICON_POWER3] Electricity.[NEWLINE] Increase [ICON_PLAGUE] Plague by +1.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WASTE_PLANT_PEDIA">
		<Text>[NEWLINE]upps[NEWLINE].</Text>
	</Row>

	<!--SAFARI-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SAFARI">
		<Text>Safari</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SAFARI_HELP">
		<Text>+5 [ICON_GOLD] Gold and +3 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture from each worked Oasis and improved source of Ivory and +25% [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism boost in this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Note[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE]City needs a improved source of Ivory and a Hotel must be build.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SAFARI_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Provides a boost in [ICON_GOLD] Gold, [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and tourism output for this City.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SAFARI_PEDIA">
		<Text>upps</Text>
	</Row>

	<!--Working Camp-->

	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_POTTER">
		<Text>Potter</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_POTTER_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Provides a little boost to [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and [ICON_GOLD] Gold</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_POTTER_PEDIA">
		<Text>"The potter is at enmity with the potter" - Hesiod (c. 800 BC - c. 720 BC)</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_POTTER_HELP">
		<Text>+1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold and [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production when [COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Writing[ENDCOLOR] is discovered.</Text>
	</Row>

	<!--Working Camp-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ARBEITSLAGER">
		<Text>Working Camp [ICON_SILVER_FIST][ICON_PLAGUE]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ARBEITSLAGER_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Provides a [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production boost and +5 [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower.[NEWLINE]-3 [ICON_HAPPINESS_4] Happines.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Increase [ICON_PLAGUE] by +2.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ARBEITSLAGER_HELP">
		<Text>+5% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production for building wonder and buildings.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Note:[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE]City requires a Dungeon.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ARBEITSLAGER_PEDIA">
		<Text>[NEWLINE]upps[NEWLINE].</Text>
	</Row>

	<!--Fire Brigade-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FEUERWEHR">
		<Text>Fire Brigade [ICON_SILVER_FIST]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FEUERWEHR_PEDIA">
		<Text>A fire department or fire brigade (also known as a fire and rescue service or simply fire service) is a public or private organization that provides predominantly emergency firefighting and rescue services for a certain jurisdiction, which typically is a municipality, county, or fire protection district. A fire department usually contains one or more fire stations within its boundaries, and may be staffed by career firefighters, volunteer firefighters, or a combination thereof referred to as a combination department. A fire department may also provide "fire protection" or fire prevention services, whereby firefighters visit homes and give fire safety advice and fit smoke alarms for members of the public. In many countries fire protection or prevention is seen as an important role for the fire service, as preventing a fire from occurring in the first place can obviously save lives. Most public or municipal fire departments also carry out an enforcement role, to ensure that commercial dwellings (hotels, offices, factories, and so on) are equipped with adequate fire precautions to ensure that in the event of fire, people can safely evacuate the premises unharmed. This is also part of the protection or prevention role.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FEUERWEHR_HELP">
		<Text>10% [ICON_FOOD] Food is saved when a new [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizen is born, +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and +1 [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness.[NEWLINE]Provides +1 [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The city needs a aquaduct.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FEUERWEHR_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Provids a boost in food and a little happiness and production boost.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_FEUERWEHR_TEXT">
		<Text>Never feared the fire?.</Text>
	</Row>

	<!--Fisher-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FISCHERHAUS">
		<Text>Fisher</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FISCHERHAUS_HELP">
		<Text>+1 [ICON_FOOD] Food for each worked Sea Resource.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Note:[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE]City requires a Dock.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FISCHERHAUS_PEDIA">
		<Text>upps.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FISCHERHAUS_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Provides a early naval [ICON_FOOD] Food boost.</Text>
	</Row>

	<!--Ski Resort-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SKI_RESORT">
		<Text>Ski Resort</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SKI_RESORT_HELP">
		<Text>Provides yields +2 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism and +4 [ICON_GOLD] Gold from worked [COLOR_YELLOW]Mountain[ENDCOLOR] tiles, +4 [ICON_GOLD] Gold from each worked [COLOR_YELLOW]Natural Wonder[ENDCOLOR].[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Note:[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE]City requires a Hotel and nearby Snow.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SKI_RESORT_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Provides a boost in [ICON_GOLD] Gold and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture for this City also it increase massiv the [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism output.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_SKI_RESORT_TEXT">
		<Text>In Europe a ski resort is a town or village in a ski area - a mountainous area, where there are ski trails and supporting services such as hotels and other accommodation, restaurants, equipment rental and a ski lift system.</Text>
	</Row>

	<!--River Port-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BINNENHAFEN">
		<Text>River Port [ICON_SILVER_FIST][ICON_PLAGUE]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BINNENHAFEN_PEDIA">
		<Text>The term inland port is also used in a narrow sense in the field of transportation systems to mean a rather more specialized facility that has come about with the advent of the intermodal container (standardized shipping container) in international transport. Rather than goods being loaded and unloaded in such ports, shipping containers can just be transferred between ship and road vehicle or ship and train. The container may be transferred again between road and rail elsewhere and the goods are only loaded or unloaded at their point of origin or final destination. Shipping containers allow some functions traditionally carried out at a seaport to be moved elsewhere. Examples are the functions of receiving, processing through customs, inspecting, sorting, and consolidating containers going to the same overseas port. Container transfer at the seaport can be sped up and container handling space can be reduced by transferring functions to an inland site away from the port and coast. Distribution may also be made more efficient by setting up the link between inland site and seaport as, say, a high-capacity rail link with a lower unit cost than sending containers individually by road. The containers are still collected from their origins or distributed to their ultimate destinations by road with the transfer happening at the inland site. An Inland Port is just such an inland site linked to a seaport. This kind of inland port does not require a waterway. Key features of an Inland Port are the transfer of containers between different modes of transportation (intermodal transfer) and the processing of international trade. This differentiates an inland port from a container depot or transport hub. The term inland port may also be used for a similar model of a site linked to an airport or land border crossing rather than a seaport. The definition of inland port in the jargon of the transportation and logistics industries is: "An Inland Port is a physical site located away from traditional land, air and coastal borders with the vision to facilitate and process international trade through strategic investment in multi-modal transportation assets and by promoting value-added services as goods move through the supply chain". — Center for Transportation Research, University of Texas. Inland Ports may also be referred to as dry ports or intermodal hubs.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BINNENHAFEN_HELP">
		<Text>+3 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production from each [COLOR_YELLOW]River[ENDCOLOR] tile and +2 [ICON_FOOD] Food for each [COLOR_YELLOW]Lake[ENDCOLOR] worked by this City.[NEWLINE]Provides +1 [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower.[NEWLINE]Increase [ICON_PLAGUE] Plague by +1.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BINNENHAFEN_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Provids a boost in [ICON_FOOD] Production and [ICON_FOOD] Food.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_BINNENHAFEN_TEXT">
		<Text>upps</Text>
	</Row>

	<!--Next-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RELIGIONSSCHULE">
		<Text>Religious School [ICON_RELIGION]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RELIGIONSSCHULE_TEXT">
		<Text>Religious School</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RELIGIONSSCHULE_HELP">
		<Text>+2 [ICON_PEACE] Faith, +1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science and +1 [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RELIGIONSSCHULE_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Provides you a [ICON_RESEARCH] Science boost and a [ICON_GREAT_WRITER] Great Writer Slot.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RELIGIONSSCHULE_PEDIA">
		<Text>Upps no text</Text>
	</Row>

	<!--Harvest-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HARVEST">
		<Text>Harvest</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HARVEST_HELP">
		<Text>+1 [ICON_PEACE] Faith and +1 [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HARVEST_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Provides a early [ICON_PEACE] Faith and [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness boost.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HARVEST_PEDIA">
		<Text>A harvest festival is an annual celebration that occurs around the time of the main harvest of a given region. Given the differences in climate and crops around the world, harvest festivals can be found at various times at different places. Harvests festivals typically feature feasting, both family and public, with foods that are drawn from crops that come to maturity around the time of the festival. Ample food and freedom from the necessity to work in the fields are two central features of harvest festivals: eating, merriment, contests, music and romance are common features of harvest festivals around the world.</Text>
	</Row>

	


	
	

	<!--Religious Sanctuary-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RELIGOSES_HEILIGTUM">
		<Text>Religious Sanctuary [ICON_RELIGION]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RELIGOSES_HEILIGTUM_HELP">
		<Text>+5 [ICON_PEACE] Faith, all [ICON_MISSIONARY] missonaries born in this city can spread [ICON_RELIGION] religion one more. Increase the [ICON_RELIGION] religious pressure[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Note[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE] Can only built in a holy city and needs the policy piety opened.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RELIGOSES_HEILIGTUM_QUOTE">
		<Text>upps</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RELIGOSES_HEILIGTUM_TEXT">
		<Text>upps</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RELIGOSES_HEILIGTUM_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Provides a big boost for your own  [ICON_RELIGION] Religion.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Increases the [ICON_RELIGION] religious pressure and [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism output of this [ICON_CAPITAL] city</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RELIGOSES_HEILIGTUM_PEDIA">
		<Text>A sanctuary, in its original meaning, is a sacred place, such as a shrine. By the use of such places as a safe haven, by extension the term has come to be used for any place of safety. This secondary use can be categorized into human sanctuary, a safe place for humans, such as a political sanctuary; and non-human sanctuary, such as an animal or plant sanctuary.</Text>
	</Row>

	<!--Folklore-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MUSIK">
		<Text>Folklore</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MUSIK_HELP">
		<Text>+10% [ICON_GREAT_PEOPLE] Great People bonus in this city.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Provides one slot for a [ICON_GREAT_MUSICIAN] Musician.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MUSIK_STRATEGY">
		<Text>More [ICON_GREAT_PEOPLE] Great People will be born, and increase the birth rate of [ICON_GREAT_MUSICIAN] Musicians.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MUSIK_TEXT">
		<Text>upps.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MUSIK_PEDIA">
		<Text>Folklore (or lore) consists of legends, music, oral history, proverbs, jokes, popular beliefs, fairy tales, stories, tall tales, and customs that are the traditions of a culture, subculture, or group. It is also the set of practices through which those expressive genres are shared. The study of folklore is sometimes called folkloristics, and people who study folklore are sometimes referred to as "folklorists". The word "folklore" was first used by the Irish antiquarian Liam Murphy in a letter published in the Tipperary journal The Athenaeum in 1846. In usage, there is a continuum between folklore and mythology. Stith Thompson made a major attempt to index the motifs of both folklore and mythology, providing an outline into which new motifs can be placed, and scholars can keep track of all older motifs. Folklore can be divided into four areas of study: artifact (such as voodoo dolls), describable and transmissible entity (oral tradition), culture, and behavior (rituals). These areas do not stand alone, however, as often a particular item or element may fit into more than one of these areas.</Text>
	</Row>

	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TAVERNE">
		<Text>Tavern</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TAVERNE_HELP">
		<Text>+1 [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] and +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold also gives a little boost to [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Note:[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE]City requires a Market and one [ICON_BREAD] Bread.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TAVERNE_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Provides a boost to [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness and [ICON_GOLD] Gold.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TAVERNE_TEXT">
		<Text>upps</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TAVERNE_PEDIA">
		<Text>A tavern is a place of business where people gather to drink alcoholic beverages and be served food, and in some cases, where travelers receive lodging. An inn is a tavern which has a license to put up guests as lodgers. The word derives from the Latin taberna whose original meaning was a shed or workshop. In the English language, a tavern was once an establishment which served wine whilst an inn served beer and ale. Over time, the words "tavern" and "inn" became interchangeable and synonymous. In England, inns started to be referred to as public houses or pubs and the term became standard for all drinking houses.</Text>
	</Row>

	<!--Gaias Shrine-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GAIA">
		<Text>Gaias Shrine</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GAIA_HELP">
		<Text>Add yields +1 [ICON_PEACE] Faith to every worked [COLOR_YELLOW]Forest[ENDCOLOR] and [COLOR_YELLOW]Jungle[ENDCOLOR] tile.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Requires[ENDCOLOR] a nearby [COLOR_YELLOW]Forest[ENDCOLOR] to be build.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GAIA_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Increase [ICON_PEACE] Faith.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GAIA_TEXT">
		<Text>Gaias Shrine.</Text>
	</Row>

	<!--BACKEREI-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BACKEREI">
		<Text>Bakery [ICON_SILVER_FIST]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_BACKEREI_TEXT">
		<Text>upps</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BACKEREI_HELP">
		<Text>Provides one free [ICON_RES_BREAD] Bread and one free [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Note:[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE]Requires one improved [ICON_WHEAT] Wheat tile.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BACKEREI_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Increase [ICON_FOOD] Food in this City and also increase the output of [ICON_MANPOWER] Manpower.</Text>
	</Row>
	

	
	<!-- Mars -->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MARS">
		<Text>Temple of Mars [ICON_RELIGION] </Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MARS_HELP">
		<Text>+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, +2 [ICON_PEACE] Faith and all land [ICON_SILVER_FIST] units builded in this city get +15 [ICON_WAR] XP.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MARS_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Provides a boost in [ICON_PEACE] Faith, [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and gives extra [ICON_WAR] XP for land [ICON_SILVER_FIST] units build in this city.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MARS_PEDIA">
		<Text>upps.</Text>
	</Row>



	<!-- Architect Office-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ARCHITEKT">
		<Text>Architect Office</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ARCHITEKT_HELP">
		<Text>+4 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and a +5% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production bonus when constructing buildings.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Note[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE] City must contain a [COLOR_YELLOW]University[ENDCOLOR] .</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ARCHITEKT_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Increase [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production for creating buildings in this city.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_ARCHITEKT_TEXT">
		<Text>upps</Text>
	</Row>


	<!--Temple of Mammon-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MAMMON">
		<Text>Temple of Mammon [ICON_RELIGION]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MAMMON_HELP">
		<Text>+2 [ICON_PEACE] Faith and +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold and +1 [ICON_PEACE] Faith for each [ICON_GEM] Gem, [ICON_SILVER] Silver or [ICON_GOLD] Gold, worked by this city</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MAMMON_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Increase your [ICON_GOLD] Gold income.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_MAMMON_TEXT">
		<Text>upps.</Text>
	</Row>

	
	
	<!--TREE-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TREE">
		<Text>Tree of Life</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_TREE_TEXT">
		<Text>upps</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TREE_HELP">
		<Text>A tall, beautiful and fruitful tree, around which your community has been founded.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Indicates this City is the [ICON_CAPITAL] Capital of the empire, until the construction of the Palace.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TREE_STRATEGY">
		<Text>The concept of a tree of life has been used in science, religion, philosophy, mythology, and other areas. A tree of life is a common motif in various world theologies, mythologies, and philosophies. A mystical concept alluding to the interconnection of all life on our planet; and a metaphor for common descent in the evolutionary sense. The term tree of life may also be used as a synonym for "sacred tree"</Text>
	</Row>

	<!--PALISADE-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PALISADE">
		<Text>Palisade</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_PALISADE_TEXT">
		<Text>upps</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PALISADE_HELP">
		<Text>Provides additional [ICON_STRENGHT] protection for your City.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PALISADE_STRATEGY">
		<Text>The Palisade is a simple, but effective City fortification. Build it to protect your community from enemy attacks.</Text>
	</Row>


	<!--Rock Paintings-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ROCK_PAINTINGS">
		<Text>Rock Paintings</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_ROCK_PAINTINGS_TEXT">
		<Text>upps</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ROCK_PAINTINGS_HELP">
		<Text>+1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Add yields +1 [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism after the discovering of [COLOR_YELLOW]Archaelogy[ENDCOLOR].[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must build near a mountain.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ROCK_PAINTINGS_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Rock Paintings increase your Civilization's [ICON_CULTURE] Culture. Millennia later, archaeologists will be in awe of your amazing work.</Text>
	</Row>


	<!--Buildings-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_LIEBE_TEXT">
		<Text>The Temple of the Goddes of love [ICON_RELIGION]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LIEBE">
		<Text>Temple of Goddes of love</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LIEBE_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Provides a [ICON_Culture] Culture, [ICON_PEACE] Faith and [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness boost.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LIEBE_HELP">
		<Text>+1 [ICON_Culture] Cultue, +2 [ICON_PEACE] Faith and +1 [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Also provide yields +1 [ICON_PEACE] Faith from each source of [ICON_RES_WINE] Vine and [ICON_RES_INCENSE] Incense worked by this city.</Text>
	</Row>

	

	<!--Bio refinery-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BIO_REFINERY">
		<Text>Bio Refinery</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BIO_REFINERY_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Build a bio refinery to increase your [ICON_RES_OIL] Oil supply.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]It will provide -2 [ICON_HAPPINESS_4] and requires a worked source of ether [ICON_RES_WHEAT] Wheat [ICON_RES_BARLEY] Barley or [ICON_RES_SUGAR] Sugar.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BIO_REFINERY_TEXT">
		<Text>Bio refinery can transform sugar, cereals or oil rich food in diesel.[NEWLINE]They are useful to increase the diesel output but will make people unhappy because of the increase in food prices.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BIO_REFINERY_HELP">
		<Text>Produces 3 [ICON_RES_OIL] oil.[NEWLINE]Requires [ICON_RES_WHEAT] Wheat [ICON_RES_BARLEY] Barley or [ICON_RES_SUGAR] Sugar and increases unhappyness.</Text>
	</Row>

	<!--Katakomben-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KATAKOMBEN">
		<Text>Catacombs</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KATAKOMBEN_HELP">
		<Text>+1 [ICON_PEACE] Faith from each [COLOR_YELLOW]Mountain[ENDCOLOR] worked by this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Requires a [COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Shrine[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must build near to a [COLOR_YELLOW]Mountain[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KATAKOMBEN_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Increase the [ICON_PEACE] Faith output of this city..</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KATAKOMBEN_TEXT">
		<Text>upps</Text>
	</Row>

	<!--Justicia-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JUSTICIA">
		<Text>Temple of Justice [ICON_RELIGION]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JUSTICIA_HELP">
		<Text>+10% [ICON_GREAT_PEOPLE] Great People in this City.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JUSTICIA_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Increase the birth rate of all [ICON_GREAT_PEOPLE] Great People in this City.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_JUSTICIA_PEDIA">
		<Text>upps</Text>
	</Row>

	<!--Hut-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HUTT">
		<Text>Hut [ICON_SILVER_FIST]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HUTT_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Build this to attract people to your town.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_HUTT_TEXT">
		<Text>Provides one extra [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizen and +25 [ICON_GOLD] Gold when finished.[NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HUTT_PEDIA">
		<Text>upps</Text>
	</Row>


	<!--Council of the elder-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_COUNCIL">
		<Text>Council of the elder</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_COUNCIL_HELP">
		<Text>+1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science and + 1 [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_COUNCIL_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Provides a [ICON_RESEARCH] Science and [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness boost.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_COUNCIL_TEXT">
		<Text>Elders are known by their interest in mentoring, sharing their long life experiences.</Text>
	</Row>

	<!--Trapper-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TRAPPER">
		<Text>Trapper</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TRAPPER_HELP">
		<Text>+1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold from [ICON_RES_FUR] Fur, [ICON_RES_IVORY] Ivory, [ICON_RES_DEER] Deer and [ICON_RES_TRUFFLES] Pigs.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Note:[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE]City must have at least one of this resources nerby improved.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TRAPPER_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Provides a small boost for [ICON_GOLD] Gold, [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and [ICON_FOOD] Food.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_TRAPPER_TEXT">
		<Text>upps</Text>
	</Row>

	<!--FOOD_STORAGE-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FOOD_STORAGE">
		<Text>Food Storage</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_FOOD_STORAGE_TEXT">
		<Text>The Food Storage is usually a cool cave or cavity, where food is kept fresh longer. Build it to increase the Growth and Wealth of your City.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FOOD_STORAGE_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Provides a little boost for [ICON_FOOD] Food and [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FOOD_STORAGE_HELP">
		<Text>+1 [ICON_FOOD] Food and +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE]Becomes obsolete with the discovery of [COLOR_YELLOW]Pottery[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
	</Row>


	<!--GEHEIMDIENST-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GEHEIMDIENST">
		<Text>Secret Agency [ICON_SPY]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_GEHEIMDIENST_TEXT">
		<Text>Secret Agency</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GEHEIMDIENST_HELP">
		<Text>Provides +1 [ICON_SPY] Spy and it grands a free unit the [ICON_SILVER_FIST] Agent.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The building [COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Military Academy[ENDCOLOR] is needed in the City and you must adopted the [ICON_CULTURE] Social Policy [COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Secret Agency [ENDCOLOR].</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GEHEIMDIENST_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Grands one free [ICON_SPY] spy that can be uses as a spy or a embassador.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GEHEIMDIENST_PEDIA">
		<Text>In espionage jargon, an agent refers to the person who does the spying; a citizen of one country who is recruited by a second country to spy on or work against his own country or a third country. In popular usage, this term is often erroneously applied to a member of an intelligence service who recruits and handles agents; in espionage such a person is referred to as an intelligence officer, intelligence operative or case officer. There are several types of agent in use today.</Text>
	</Row>

	<!--PLASTIKFABRIK-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PLASTIKFABRIK">
		<Text>Plastic Factory</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PLASTIKFABRIK_HELP">
		<Text>+10% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production in this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Requries one resource of [COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Oil and Electricty[ENDCOLOR] to build.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PLASTIKFABRIK_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Provides a boost for [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_PLASTIKFABRIK_TEXT">
		<Text>Plastics engineering encompasses the processing, design, development, and manufacture of plastics products. A plastic is a polymeric material that is in a semi-liquid state, having the property of plasticity and exhibiting flow. Plastics engineering encompasses plastics material and plastic machinery. Plastic Machinery is the general term for all types of machinery and devices used in the plastics processing industry. The nature of plastic materials poses unique challenges to an engineer. Mechanical properties of plastics are often difficult to quantify, and the plastics engineer has to design a product that meets certain specifications while keeping costs to a minimum. Other properties that the plastics engineer has to address include; outdoor weatherability, thermal properties such as upper use temperature, electrical properties, barrier properties, and resistance to chemical attack.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_PLASTIKFABRIK_PEDIA">
		<Text>upps</Text>
	</Row>
	
	<!--Bonfire-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BONFIRE">
		<Text>Bonfire</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BONFIRE_PEDIA">
		<Text>upps</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BONFIRE_STRATEGY">
		<Text>The Bonfire increases your [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizens [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Build it when your city grows larger to avoid an unhappy nation.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_BONFIRE_TEXT">
		<Text>+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and +2 [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Oblosolete with [COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Calendar[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
	</Row>

	<!--SYNTHETIC_PETROL_PLANT-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SYNTHETIC_PETROL_PLANT">
		<Text>Synthetic Petrol Plant</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SYNTHETIC_PETROL_PLANT_TEXT">
		<Text>Synthetic fuel is a liquid fuel obtained from [ICON_RES_COAL] coal, natural gas, oil shale, or biomass. It may also refer to fuels derived from other solids such as plastics or rubber waste. It may also (less often) refer to gaseous fuels produced in a similar way. Common use of the term "synthetic fuel" is to describe fuels manufactured via Fischer Tropsch conversion, methanol to gasoline conversion, or direct coal liquefaction. Direct conversion of coal to synthetic fuel was originally developed in Germany. Synthetic fuel grades included, "first quality aviation gasoline", "aviation base gasoline" and "gasoline - middle oil"; "producer gas" and diesel were synthesized for fuel as well (e.g., converted armored tanks used producer gas). By early 1944, German synthetic fuel production had reached more than 124,000 barrels per day. July 2009 worldwide commercial synthetic fuels production capacity is over 240,000 barrels per day, with numerous new projects in construction or development.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SYNTHETIC_PETROL_PLANT_STRATEGY">
		<Text>If you don't have enough crude [ICON_RES_OIL] Oil supply and don't wan't to start a war for it the Synthetic Petrol Plant is the solution![NEWLINE][NEWLINE]It will convert your spared Coal into high grade aviation gasoline and Diesel.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SYNTHETIC_PETROL_PLANT_HELP">
		<Text>This building requires 5 [ICON_RES_COAL] Coal and will provide 3 [ICON_RES_DIESEL] Diesel and 3 [ICON_RES_KEROSENE] Kerosene.</Text>
	</Row>

	<!--STEEL_FOUNDRY-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_STEEL_FOUNDRY">
		<Text>Steel Foundry [ICON_SILVER_FIST]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_STEEL_FOUNDRY_HELP">
		<Text>Requires 1 [ICON_RES_COAL] Coal and 2 [ICON_RES_IRON].[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Provides +5 [ICON_RES_STEEL] Steel and +1 [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_STEEL_FOUNDRY_STRATEGY">
		<Text>A Steel Foundry provides provides you with the [ICON_RES_STEEL] steel needed for [ICON_WAR] advanced weapons.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_STEEL_FOUNDRY_TEXT">
		<Text>A foundry is a factory that produces metal castings. Metals are cast into shapes by melting them into a liquid, pouring the metal in a mold, and removing the mold material or casting after the metal has solidified as it cools. The most common metals processed are aluminum and cast iron. However, other metals, such as steel, magnesium, copper, tin, and zinc, are also used to produce castings in foundries.</Text>
	</Row>

	
	<!--SHELTER-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SHELTER_TITLE">
		<Text>Shelter</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SHELTER_DESC">
		<Text>Lean-to Shelter</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SHELTER_HELP">
		<Text>Provides [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Happiness[ENDCOLOR] in your community.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Becomes [COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Obsolete[ENDCOLOR] with the discovery of [COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Masonry[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SHELTER_STATEGY">
		<Text>The basic stick shelter is one of the most primitive of shelters, still in use today. Its great advantage was the portable nature of the core components. It could also be built almost anywhere. Simple to set up, it protects only against the basic elements.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Provides [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Happiness[ENDCOLOR] for your community as they are able to shelter themselves from some environmental elements.
		</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SHELTER_PEDIA">
		<Text>Shelter</Text>
	</Row>
	
	
	<!--SAMMLER)-->

<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_SAMMLER_TEXT">
	<Text>Collector</Text>
</Row>	
<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SAMMLER_HELP">
	<Text>Adds yields +2 [ICON_FOOD] Food.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Obsolete[ENDCOLOR] with the discovery of [COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Economy of Scale[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
</Row>
<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SAMMLER_STRATEGY">
	<Text>Provides a boost to [ICON_FOOD] Food for this city.</Text>
</Row>
<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SAMMLER_DESC">
	<Text>Collector</Text>
</Row>

	<!--WASSERSPEICHER-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WASSERSPEICHER_DESC">
		<Text>Water Reservoir [ICON_HEALTH]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WASSERSPEICHER_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Provides a [ICON_FOOD] Food bost for each [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizen in this city.[NEWLINE]Increase [ICON_HEALTH] Health by +1.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WASSERSPEICHER_HELP">
		<Text>Provides +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food for every [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizen in this city.[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT][ENDCOLOR] [NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Obsolete[ENDCOLOR] with the discovery of [COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Sanitation[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_WASSERSPEICHER_TEXT">
		<Text></Text>
	</Row>
		
	<!--MILKA-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MILKA">
		<Text>Milkfarm</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MILKA_HELP">
			<Text>Adds yields +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food for every [ICON_RES_COW] Cow and [ICON_RES_SHEEP] Sheep resources worked by this city.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Requirement[ENDCOLOR]City needs a improved source of one of this resources.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MILKA_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Provides a boost forwards [ICON_FOOD] Food and also increase the [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production in the city.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_MILKA_TEXT">
		<Text>Humans first learned to regularly consume the milk of other mammals following the domestication of animals during the Neolithic Revolution or the development of agriculture. This development occurred independently in several places around the world from as early as 9000–7000 BC in Southwest Asia to 3500–3000 BC in the Americas. The most important dairy animals—cattle, sheep and goats—were first domesticated in Southwest Asia, although domestic cattle has been independently derived from wild aurochs populations several times since. Initially animals were kept for meat, and archaeologist Andrew Sherratt has suggested that dairying, along with the exploitation of domestic animals for hair and labor, began much later in a separate secondary products revolution in the 4th millennium BC.[27] Sherratt's model is not supported by recent findings, based on the analysis of lipid residue in prehistoric pottery, that show that dairying was practiced in the early phases of agriculture in Southwest Asia, by at least the 7th millennium BC.From Southwest Asia domestic dairy animals spread to Europe (beginning around 7000 BC but not reaching Britain and Scandinavia until after 4000 BC),[30] and South Asia (7000–5500 BC).[31] The first farmers in central Europe[32] and Britain[33] milked their animals. Pastoral and pastoral nomadic economies, which rely predominantly or exclusively on domestic animals and their products rather than crop farming, were developed as European farmers moved into the Pontic-Caspian steppe in the 4th millennium BC, and subsequently spread across much of the Eurasian steppe.[34] Sheep and goats were introduced to Africa from Southwest Asia, but African cattle may have been independently domesticated around 7000–6000 BC. Camels, domesticated in central Arabia in the 4th millennium BC, have also been used as a dairy animal in North Africa and the Arabian peninsula. The earliest Egyptian records of burn treatment describe burn dressings using milk from mothers of male babies. In the rest of the world (i.e., East and Southeast Asia, the Americas and Australia) milk and dairy products were historically not a large part of the diet, either because they remained populated by hunter-gatherers who did not keep animals or the local agricultural economies did not include domesticated dairy species. Milk consumption became common in these regions comparatively recently, as a consequence of European colonialism and political domination over much of the world in the last 500 years. In the Middle Ages, milk was called the virtuous white liquor because alcoholic beverages were more reliable than water.
		</Text>
	</Row>
		
	<!--HORSEMAN-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HORSEMAN">
		<Text>Horse Breeder [ICON_RES_MANPOWER]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HORSEMAN_HELP">
		<Text>Provides +1 [ICON_RES_IRON] Iron.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Add yields +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold for every worked source of [ICON_RES_IRON] Iron.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Requires[ENDCOLOR] 2 [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HORSEMAN_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Grands one resource [ICON_RES_IRON] Iron, but requires two resources [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Gives a little [ICON_GOLD] Gold and [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production boost to the city.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_HORSEMAN_TEXT">
		<Text>A horse breed is a selectively bred population of domesticated horses, often with pedigrees recorded in a breed registry. However, the term is sometimes used in a very broad sense to define landrace animals, or naturally selected horses of a common phenotype located within a limited geographic region. Depending on definition, hundreds of "breeds" exist today, developed for many different uses. Horse breeds are loosely divided into three categories based on general temperament: spirited "hot bloods" with speed and endurance; "cold bloods," such as draft horses and some ponies, suitable for slow, heavy work; and "warmbloods," developed from crosses between hot bloods and cold bloods, often focusing on creating breeds for specific riding purposes, particularly in Europe. Horse breeds are groups of horses with distinctive characteristics that are transmitted consistently to their offspring, such as conformation, color, performance ability, or disposition. These inherited traits are usually the result of a combination of natural crosses and artificial selection methods aimed at producing horses for specific tasks. Certain breeds are known for certain talents. For example, Standardbreds are known for their speed in harness racing. Some breeds have been developed through centuries of crossings with other breeds, while others, such as Tennessee Walking Horses and Morgans, developed from a single sire from which all current breed members descend. There are more than 300 horse breeds in the world today.</Text>
	</Row>


	<!--RADIOACTICMAN-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RADIOACTICMAN">
		<Text>Deep Uranium Mine [ICON_RES_MANPOWER]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RADIOACTICMAN_HELP">
		<Text>Provides +1 [ICON_RES_URANIUM] Uranium.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Add yields +1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science and +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production for every worked source of [ICON_RES_URANIUM] Uranium.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Requires[ENDCOLOR] 10 [ICON_RES_MANPOWER]Manpower.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_RADIOACTICMAN_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Grands one resource [ICON_RES_URANIUM] Uranium, but requires two resources [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Gives a little [ICON_GOLD] Gold and [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production boost to the city.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_RADIOACTICMAN_TEXT">
		<Text>upps</Text>
	</Row>



	<!--OELMAN-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_OILMAN">
		<Text>Large Oil Field [ICON_RES_MANPOWER]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_OILMAN_HELP">
		<Text>Provides +1 [ICON_RES_OIL] Oil.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Add yields +2 [ICON_GOLD] Science and +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production for every worked source of [ICON_RES_OIL] Oil.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Requires[ENDCOLOR]8 [ICON_RES_MANPOWER]Manpower.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_OILMAN_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Grands one resource [ICON_RES_ALU] ALU, but requires eight [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Gives a little [ICON_GOLD] Gold and [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production boost to the city.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_OILMAN_TEXT">
		<Text>upps</Text>
	</Row>



	<!--ALUMAN-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ALUMAN">
		<Text>Deep Aluminium Mine [ICON_RES_MANPOWER]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ALUMAN_HELP">
		<Text>Provides +1 [ICON_RES_ALUMINUM] Aluminum.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Add yields +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production for every worked source of [ICON_RES_ALUMINUM] Aluminum.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Requires[ENDCOLOR]8 [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ALUMAN_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Grands one resource [ICON_RES_ALUMINUM] Aluminum, but requires 8 [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Gives a little [ICON_GOLD] Gold and [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production boost to the city.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_ALUMAN_TEXT">
		<Text>upps.</Text>
	</Row>

	<!--GEWURZHAUS-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GEWURZHAUS_HELP">
		<Text>+5% [ICON_FOOD] Food is saved when a new [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizen is born.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Provides one additional luxury resource [ICON_RES_SPICE] Spice.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Add yields +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold +1 [ICON_FOOD]  Food.[NEWLINE][COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Requires[ENDCOLOR] 4 [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower to be build.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have a improved source of [ICON_RES_SPICE] Spice.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GEWURZHAUS">
		<Text>Spice House [ICON_RES_MANPOWER]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GEWURZHAUS_STRATEGY">
	<Text>Grands one luxury resource [ICON_RES_SPICE] Spices.[NEWLINE][COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Requires[ENDCOLOR] 4 [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Gives a little [ICON_GOLD] Gold and [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production boost to the city.</Text>
   </Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_GEWURZHAUS_TEXT">
		<Text>A spice may be available in several forms: fresh, whole dried, or pre-ground dried.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Generally, spices are dried. A whole dried spice has the longest shelf life, so it can be purchased and stored in larger amounts, making it cheaper on a per-serving basis.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Some spices are not always available either fresh or whole, for example turmeric, and must commonly, be purchased in ground form. Small seeds, such as fennel and mustard seeds, are often used both whole and in powder form.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The flavor of a spice is derived in part from compounds (volatile oils) that oxidize or evaporate when exposed to air. Grinding a spice greatly increases its surface area and so increases the rates of oxidation and evaporation. Thus, flavor is maximized by storing a spice whole and grinding when needed.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The shelf life of a whole dry spice is roughly two years; of a ground spice roughly six months. The "flavor life" of a ground spice can be much shorter. Ground spices are better stored away from light.</Text>
	</Row>


	<!--ELFENBEINSTUBE-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ELFENBEINSTUBE_HELP">
		<Text>Provides one additional luxury resources of [ICON_RES_IVORY] Ivory.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Add yields +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food and [ICON_Culture] Culture to each [ICON_RES_IVORY] Ivory.[NEWLINE][COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Requires[ENDCOLOR] 4 [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have a improved source of [ICON_RES_IVORY] Ivory.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ELFENBEINSTUBE">
		<Text>Ivory artist [ICON_RES_MANPOWER]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ELFENBEINSTUBE_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Grands one luxury resource [ICON_RES_IVORY] Ivory, but requires 4 [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Gives a little [ICON_GOLD] Gold and [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production boost to the city.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_ELFENBEINSTUBE_TEXT">
		<Text>Ivory carving is the carving of ivory, that is to say animal tooth or tusk, by using sharp cutting tools, either mechanically or manually. Humans have ornamentally carved ivory since prehistoric times, though until the 19th century opening-up of the interior of Africa, it was usually a rare and expensive material used for luxury products. Very fine detail can be achieved, and as the material, unlike precious metals, has no bullion value and usually cannot easily be recycled, the survival rate for ivory pieces is much higher than for those in other materials. Ivory carving has a special importance to the medieval art of Europe and Byzantium because of this, and in particular as so little monumental sculpture was produced or has survivedIvory is by no means just obtained from elephants; any animal tooth or tusk used as a material for carving may be termed "ivory", though the species is usually added, and a great number of different species with tusks or large teeth have been used. Teeth have three elements: the outer dental enamel, then the main body of dentine, and the inner root of osteo-dentine. For the purposes of carving the last two are in most animals both usable, but the harder enamel may be too hard to carve, and require removal by grinding first. This is the case with hippopotamus for example, whose tooth enamel (on the largest teeth) is about as hard as jade. Elephant ivory, as well as coming in the largest pieces, is relatively soft and even, and an ideal material for carving. The species of animal from which ivory comes can usually be determined by examination under ultra-violet light, where different types show different colours Eurasian elephant ivory was usually obtained from the tusks of elephants in India, and in Roman times, from North Africa; from the 18th century sub-Saharan Africa became the main source. Ivory harvesting led to the extinction, or near-extinction of elephants in much of their former range. In early medieval Northern Europe, walrus ivory was traded south from as far away as Norse Greenland to Scandinavia, southern England and northern France and Germany. In Siberia and Arctic North America, mammoth tusks could be recovered from permafrost and used; this became a large business in the 19th century, with convicts used for much of the labour. The 25,000 year-old Venus of Brassempouy, arguably the earliest real likeness of a human face, was carved from mammoth ivory no doubt freshly killed. In northern Europe during the Early Middle Ages walrus ivory was more easily obtained from Viking traders, and later Norse settlements in Greenland than elephant ivory from the south; at this time walrus were probably found much further south than they are today. Sperm whale teeth are another source, and bone carving has been used in many cultures without access to ivory, and as a far cheaper alternative; in the Middle Ages whalebone was often used, either from the Basque whaling industry or natural strandings.</Text>
	</Row>



	<!--CIGARS-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CIGARS_HELP">
		<Text>Provides 2 additional luxury resources of [ICON_RES_CIGARS] Cigars.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Requires[ENDCOLOR]  4 [ICON_RES_TOBACCO] Tobacco and 4 [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower to be build.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CIGARS">
		<Text>Cigars Shop [ICON_RES_MANPOWER]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CIGARS_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Grands 2 luxury resource [ICON_RES_CIGARS] Cigars, but requires 4 [ICON_RES_TOBACCO] Tobacco and 4 [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_CIGARS_TEXT">
		<Text>The word cigar originated from the Spanish cigarro, which in turn probably derives from the Mayan sicar ("to smoke rolled tobacco leaves" – from si'c, "tobacco;"). There is also a possible derivation, or at least an influence, from the Spanish cigarra ("cicada"), due to their similar shape. The English word came into general use in 1730.</Text>
	</Row>




	<!--WEBSTUBE-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WEBSTUBE">
			<Text>Weaver</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WEBSTUBE_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Adds yields 1+ [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production from each worked source of [ICON_RES_COW] Cow, [ICON_RES_SHEEP], [ICON_RES_FUR] Fur, and [ICON_RES_DEER] Deer.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WEBSTUBE_HELP">
			<Text>Adds yields 1+ [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production from each worked source of [ICON_RES_COW] Cow, [ICON_RES_SHEEP], [ICON_RES_FUR] Fur, and [ICON_RES_DEER] Deer.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Note:[ENDCOLOR]Requires one of this Resources nearby improved.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_WEBSTUBE_TEXT">
			<Text>Weaving is a method of fabric production in which two distinct sets of yarns or threads are interlaced at right angles to form a fabric or cloth. The other methods are knitting, lace making, felting, and braiding or plaiting. The longitudinal threads are called the warp and the lateral threads are the weft or filling. (Weft or woof is an old English word meaning "that which is woven".) The method in which these threads are inter woven affects the characteristics of the cloth. Cloth is usually woven on a loom, a device that holds the warp threads in place while filling threads are woven through them. A fabric band which meets this definition of cloth (warp threads with a weft thread winding between) can also be made using other methods, including tablet weaving, back-strap, or other techniques without looms. The way the warp and filling threads interlace with each other is called the weave. The majority of woven products are created with one of three basic weaves: plain weave, satin weave, or twill. Woven cloth can be plain (in one colour or a simple pattern), or can be woven in decorative or artistic designs.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!--SKLAVENMARKT-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SKLAVENMARKT">
			<Text>Slave Market [ICON_SILVER_FIST][ICON_PLAGUE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SKLAVENMARKT_STRATEGY">
			<Text>+5% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production when creating Buildings or Wonders.[NEWLINE]-5 [ICON_HAPPINESS_4] Happines.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Allowes to transport [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production via [ICON_CARAVAN] Caravans.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SKLAVENMARKT_HELP">
			<Text>Wonders and Buildings get a +5% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production bonus.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Provides +5 [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower.[NEWLINE]Reduce the local [ICON_HAPPIENSS_4] Happiness by -2.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Increase [ICON_PLAGUE] Plague by +1.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SKLAVENMARKT_PEDIA">
			<Text>The history of slavery traces the history of slavery and the slave trade from ancient times to the present. Slavery is a legally recognised system in which people are legally considered the property or chattel of another.[1] A slave had few rights and could be bought or sold and made to work for the owner without any choice or pay. As Drescher (2009) argues, "The most crucial and frequently utilized aspect of the condition is a communally recognized right by some individuals to possess, buy, sell, discipline, transport, liberate, or otherwise dispose of the bodies and behavior of other individuals."[2] In the American colonies and other places, an integral element was frequently the assignment of children of a slave mother to the status of slaves - born into slavery.[3] Slavery does not include other forced labor systems: historical forced labor by prisoners, labor camps, or other forms of unfree labor, in which laborers are not considered property.</Text>
		</Row>

		<!--FREUDENHAUS-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FREUDENHAUS">
			<Text>Brothel [ICON_PLAGUE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FREUDENHAUS_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Provides a boost for the [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness in the city.[NEWLINE]Increase [ICON_PLAGUE] Plague in this city by +1.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have a Tavern.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]+1[ICON_TOURISM] Tourism[ENDCOLOR].[NEWLINE]When [COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Touristic[ENDCOLOR] is discovered.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FREUDENHAUS_HELP">
			<Text>+4 [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Add yields +1 [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism when Touristic is researched.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FREUDENHAUS_PEDIA">
			<Text>A brothel is a place where people may come to engage in sexual activity with a prostitute, sometimes referred to as a sex worker. Technically, any premises where prostitution commonly takes place qualifies as a brothel, however for legal or cultural reasons establishments may describe themselves as massage parlors, bars, strip clubs or by some other description. Sex work in a brothel is considered safer than street prostitution</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!--MENHIR-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MENHIR">
			<Text>Menhir</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MENHIR_HELP">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_PEACE] Faith.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Obsolete[ENDCOLOR] with the discovery of [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Leadership[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MENHIR_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Provides a early boost to [ICON_PEACE] Faith and [ICON_CULTURE] Culture in this city.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Add yields +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture when Calendar is discovered.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MENHIR_PEDIA">
			<Text>A menhir (French, from Middle Breton: men, "stone" and hir, "long"), standing stone, orthostat, or lith is a large upright standing stone. Menhirs may be found singly as monoliths, or as part of a group of similar stones. Their size can vary considerably, but their shape is generally uneven and squared, often tapering towards the top. Menhirs are widely distributed across Europe, Africa and Asia, but are most numerous in Western Europe; in particular in Ireland, Great Britain and Brittany. There are about 50,000 megaliths in these areas, while there are 1,200 menhirs in northwest France alone. Standing stones are usually difficult to date, but pottery found underneath some in Atlantic Europe connects them with the Beaker people. They were constructed during many different periods across pre-history, erected as part of a larger megalithic culture that flourished in Europe and beyond. Some menhirs have been raised next to buildings which often have some early or current religious significance. One example is the South Zeal Menhir in Devon, which formed the basis for a 12th-century monastery built by lay monks. The monastery later became the Oxenham Arms Hotel at South Zeal, and the standing stone remains in place in the ancient snug bar at the hotel. Where they appear in groups, often in a circular, oval, henge or horseshoe formation, they are sometimes called megalithic monuments. These are sites of ancient religious ceremonies, sometimes containing burial chambers. The exact function of menhirs has provoked more debate than practically any other issue in European pre-history. Over the centuries, they have variously been thought to have been used by Druids for human sacrifice, used as territorial markers or elements of a complex ideological system, or functioned as early calendars. Until the nineteenth century, antiquarians did not have substantial knowledge of prehistory; and their only reference points were provided by Classical literature. The developments of radiocarbon dating and tree-ring calibration have done much to further knowledge in this area. The word menhir was adopted from French by 19th century archaeologists. It is a combination of two words found in the Breton language; men and hir. In modern Welsh, they are described as maen hir, or "long stone". In modern Breton, the word peulvan is used.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!--TOWN_SQUARE-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TOWN_SQUARE">
			<Text>Town Square [ICON_SILVER_FIST]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TOWN_SQUARE_HELP">
			<Text>Add yields +1 [ICON_GOLD] and +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Increase also [ICON_Gold] Gold from [ICON_INTERNATIONAL_TRADE] trade routes.[NEWLINE]Provides +1 [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TOWN_SQUARE_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Provides a early boost to [ICON_GOLD] Gold in this city.[NEWLINE]Also increases the[ICON_Gold] Gold income frome [ICON_INTERNATIONAL_TRADE] trade routes.[NEWLINE]Add yields +1 [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism when Archaeology is discovered.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_TOWN_SQUARE_TEXT">
			<Text>In urban planning, a city square or urban square is a planned open area in a city, usually or originally rectangular in shape. Some city squares are large enough that they act as a sort of "national square". The first urban formations started appearing at least 6000 years ago. Within urban areas open public space always existed and it served a very important purpose. Along with the development of human society and the development of cities, the squares acquired more and more functions. At first, the squares were established at the crossroads of important trade routes where exchange of goods as well as ideas took place. For example, Phoenician trades–people invented numerical and linguistic pictographic inscriptions out of the need to record transactions. Another very important function of the public square was that it served as an opportunity to exercise the power of rulers with military processions and parades. Wars led to cities surrounded by thick walls and elaborate systems of defense. These became very densely populated, but even under these conditions there was always room for an open public space. Its functions were expanding too. Major places of worship were placed there, squares were used as permanent or temporary markets, monuments to important predecessors were erected and revolutions or contra-revolutions were staged. The squares became the location of royal courts, government buildings and city halls as manifestations of wealth and power. They were also used for races, like the Palio race in Siena, bull fights, executions, or even just to collect rain water in large underground cisterns.</Text>
		</Row>
		
	
		<!--PERLENTAUCHER-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PERLENTAUCHER">
			<Text>Pearl Divers</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PERLENTAUCHER_HELP">
			<Text>+2 [ICON_Gold] Gold, +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food, for every [ICON_RES_PEARLS] Pearls source worked by this city.[NEWLINE][COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Requires[ENDCOLOR] 2 [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PERLENTAUCHER_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Provides one free source of [ICON_RES_PEARLS].[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Needs 2 [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower and a improved source of [ICON_RES_PEARLS] Pearls to build.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must contain docks.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PERLENTAUCHER_PEDIA">
			<Text>Before the beginning of the 20th century, the only means of obtaining pearls was by manually gathering very large numbers of pearl oysters (or pearl mussels) from the ocean floor (or lake, or river bottom). The bivalves were then brought to the surface, opened, and the tissues searched. More than a ton were searched in order to find at least 3-4 quality pearls. In order to find enough pearl oysters, free-divers were often forced to descend to depths of over 100 feet on a single breath, exposing them to the dangers of hostile creatures, waves, eye damage, and drowning, often as a result of shallow water blackout on resurfacing.</Text>
		</Row>


		<!--KRABBENFISCHER-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KRABBENFISCHER">
			<Text>Crab Fisher</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KRABBENFISCHER_HELP">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_Gold] Gold, +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food, for every [ICON_RES_CRAB] Crab source worked by this city.[NEWLINE][COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Requires[ENDCOLOR] 2 [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KRABBENFISCHER_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Provides one free source of [ICON_RES_CRABS].[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Needs 2 [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower and a improved source of [ICON_RES_CRAB] Crab to be build.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must contain docks.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_KRABBENFISCHER_PEDIA">
			<Text>Crab fisheries are fisheries which capture or farm crabs. True crabs make up 20% of all crustaceans caught and farmed worldwide, with about 1.4 million tonnes being consumed annually. The horse crab, Portunus trituberculatus accounts for one quarter of that total. Other important species include flower crabs (Portunus pelagicus), snow crabs (Chionoecetes), blue crabs (Callinectes sapidus), edible or brown crabs (Cancer pagurus), Dungeness crab (Metacarcinus magister) and mud crabs (Scylla serrata), each of which provides more than 20,000 tonnes annually.</Text>
		</Row>


	<!--WALFANGERHAUS-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WALFANGERHAUS">
		<Text>Whale Hunter</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WALFANGERHAUS_HELP">
		<Text>+2 [ICON_Gold] Gold, +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and +2 [ICON_FOOD] Food, for every [ICON_RES_WHALE] Whale source worked by this city.[NEWLINE]5% [ICON_FOOD] Food is saved after a new [ICON_CITIZEN] citizen is bornin this city.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Requires[ENDCOLOR] 3 [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WALFANGERHAUS_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Provides one free source of [ICON_RES_WHALE].[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Needs 3 [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower and a improved source of [ICON_RES_WHALE] Whale to be build.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must contain docks.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_WALFANGERHAUS_TEXT">
		<Text>Whaling is the hunting of whales primarily for meat and oil. Its earliest forms date to at least 3000 BC. Various coastal communities have long histories of subsistence whaling and harvesting beached whales. Industrial whaling emerged with organized fleets in the 17th century; competitive national whaling industries in the 18th and 19th centuries; and the introduction of factory ships along with the concept of whale harvesting in the first half of the 20th century. As technology increased and demand for the resources remained, catches far exceeded the sustainable limit for whale stocks. In the late 1930s, more than 50,000 whales were killed annually and by the middle of the century whale stocks were not being replenished. In 1986, the International Whaling Commission (IWC) banned commercial whaling so that stocks might recover.</Text>
	</Row>

	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TAXCOLLECTOR">
		<Text>Tax Collector [ICON_CRIME]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TAXCOLLECTOR_HELP">
		<Text>Provides +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold for each 2 [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizen in this city.[NEWLINE]Reduce the local [ICON_HAPPINESS_4] Happiness by -1.[NEWLINE]Increase [ICON_CRIME] Crime by +3.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Note:[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE]City requires a Market.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TAXCOLLECTOR_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Provides a boost for [ICON_GOLD] Gold, for each 2 [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizen to the city.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_TAXCOLLECTOR_PEDIA">
		<Text>Tax collectors, also known as publicans, are mentioned many times in the Bible (mainly in the New Testament). They were working for tax farmers. They are generally described as being greedy, and taking more money than they are entitled to. In the Gospel of Luke, Jesus sympathises with the tax collector Zacchaeus, causing outrage from the crowds that Jesus would rather be the guest of a sinner than of a more respectable or "righteous" person. Saint Matthew in the New Testament was a tax collector.</Text>
	</Row>
	
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CARPENTER">
		<Text>Carpenter [ICON_RES_MANPOWER]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CARPENTER_TEXT">
		<Text>Wood is one of mankind's oldest building materials. The ability to shape wood improved with technological advances from the stone age to the bronze age to the iron age. Relatively little information about carpentry is available from pre-history (before written language) or even recent centuries because the knowledge and skills were passed down person to person, rarely in writing, until the printing press was invented in the 15th century and builders began regularly publishing guides and pattern books in the 18th and 19th centuries. The oldest surviving, complete architectural text is Vitruvius' ten books collectively titled De architectura which discusses some carpentry. Some of the oldest, surviving, wooden buildings in the world are the temples in China such as the Nanchan Temple built in the year 782, the Greensted Church parts of which are from the 11th century, the stave churchs in Norway from the 12th and 13th centuries. By the 16th century sawmills were coming into use in Europe. The founding of America was partly based on a desire to extract resources from the new continent including wood for use in ships and buildings in Europe. In the 18th century part of the Industrial Revolution was the invention of the steam engine and cut nails. These technologies combined with the invention of the circular saw led to the development of balloon framing which was the beginning of the decline of traditional timber framing. The 19th century saw the development of electrical engineering and distribution which allowed the development of hand-held power tools, wire nails and machines to mass-produce screws. In the 20th century portland cement came into common use and concrete foundations allowed carpenters to do away with heavy timber sills. Also, drywall came into common use replacing lime plaster on wooden lath. Plywood, engineered lumber and chemically treated lumber also came into use.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CARPENTER_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Provides one [ICON_RES_TURKISHCARPETS] Carpet.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Requires[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE]2 [ICON_RES_LINEN] Linen and also 2 [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower to be build.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CARPENTER_HELP">
		<Text>Provides one [ICON_RES_TURKISHCARPETS] Carpet.</Text>
	</Row>
	<!--MENHIR-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SUPPLY_HOUSE">
		<Text>Supply House [ICON_SILVER_FIST]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SUPPLY_HOUSE_HELP">
		<Text>Provides three [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower resources.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Requires[ENDCOLOR] the building [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Granary[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SUPPLY_HOUSE_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Provides a early support for usefull [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] manpower resources.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Add yields +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production when [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Slavery[ENDCOLOR] is discovered.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SUPPLY_HOUSE_PEDIA">
		<Text></Text>
	</Row>

	<!--BEWASSERUNGSSYSTEM-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BEWASSERUNGSSYSTEM">
		<Text>Water System [ICON_HEALTH]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BEWASSERUNGSSYSTEM_HELP">
		<Text>Add yields +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food to every lake worked by this city.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Increase the [ICON_HEALTH] Health in this city by +1.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BEWASSERUNGSSYSTEM_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Provides a boost to [ICON_FOOD] Food and [ICON_HEALTH] Health.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Note:[ENDCOLOR] City must have a source of fresh Water.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BEWASSERUNGSSYSTEM_PEDIA">
		<Text>The oldest known canals were irrigation canals, built in Mesopotamia circa 4000 BC, in what is now Iraq and Syria. The Indus Valley Civilization, Ancient India, (circa 2600 BC) had sophisticated irrigation and storage systems developed, including the reservoirs built at Girnar in 3000 BC. In Egypt, canals date back at least to the time of Pepi I Meryre (reigned 2332–2283 BC), who ordered a canal built to bypass the cataract on the Nile near Aswan.</Text>
	</Row>



	<!--COPPERSMITH-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_COPPERSMITH">
		<Text>Copper Smith [ICON_SILVER_FIST]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_COPPERSMITH_HELP">
		<Text>+1 [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower.[NEWLINE]All new trained military land [ICON_SILVER_FIST] units get the free Promotion Bronze Weapons.[NEWLINE]Add yields +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production to each worked source oc Copper.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Requires[ENDCOLOR]a nearby improved source of Copper to be build.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_COPPERSMITH_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Provides a boost forward to [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and increse the amount of [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_COPPERSMITH_TEXT">
		<Text>A coppersmith, also known as a redsmith, is a person who makes artifacts from copper. The term redsmith comes from the colour of copper.</Text>
	</Row>


	<!--IRONMAN-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_IRONMAN">
		<Text>Deep Iron Mine [ICON_RES_MANPOWER]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_IRONMAN_HELP">
		<Text>Provides +2 [ICON_RES_IRON] Iron.[NEWLINE]Requires a nearby improved source of Iron.[NEWLINE]Also 2 [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower are needed.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_IRONMAN_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Increase the amount of [ICON_RES_IRON] Iron, but requires [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_IRONMAN_TEXT">
		<Text>upps</Text>
	</Row>


	<!--COALMAN-->
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_COALMAN">
		<Text>Deep Coal Mine [ICON_RES_MANPOWER]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_COALMAN_HELP">
		<Text>Provides one free source of [ICON_RES_COAL] Coal.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Add yields +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold and +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production to each worked of source of [ICON_RES_COAL] Coal.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Requires[ENDCOLOR] a improved source of [ICON_RES_COAL] Coal and ten [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT][ENDCOLOR]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_COALMAN_STRATEGY">
		<Text>Build it to use [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower to create one free source of [ICON_RES_COAL] Coal.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_COALMAN_TEXT">
		<Text>Coal remains an important energy source, due to its low cost and abundance when compared to other fuels, particularly for electricity generation. Coal is also mined today on a large scale by open pit methods wherever the coal strata strike the surface or are relatively shallow. Britain developed the main techniques of underground coal mining from the late 18th century onward with further progress being driven by 19th century and early 20th century progress. However, oil and its associated fuels began to be used as alternative from the 1860s onward.</Text>
	</Row>

	<Update>
		<Set Text="Greatly increases [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness in the empire."/>
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_FORBIDDEN_PALACE_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="City must be built on or next to Desert. +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food, +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, and +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold for all desert tiles worked by this city (except Flood Plains)."/>
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_PETRA_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="1 Free Social Policy.[NEWLINE]Must be constructed in a coastal city."/>
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_SYDNEY_OPERA_HOUSE_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<!--<Update>
			<Set Text="A Great Artist appears in the City where this building was constructed."/>
			<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_HAGIA_SOPHIA_HELP" />
		</Update>-->
	<Update>
		<Set Text="+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production from Artist Specialist in every City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Must have built a Monument in all Cities. The cost goes up the more cities there are in the empire."/>
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NATIONAL_EPIC_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="+1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold from Artist Specialist in every City."/>
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_SISTINE_CHAPEL_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="+1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science from Scientist Specialist in every City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]1 Free Technology.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Must have built a University in all Cities. The cost goes up the more cities there are in the empire."/>
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_OXFORD_UNIVERSITY_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="City must be built next to a River or Lake."/>
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GARDEN_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="Greatly increases [ICON_CULTURE] Culture in this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have a Museum."/>
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BROADCAST_TOWER_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="City must have a Bank."/>
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_STOCK_EXCHANGE_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="City must have a Market."/>
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BANK_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="Each source of [ICON_RES_IRON] Iron worked by this City produces +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have a Military Academy."/>
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_ARSENAL_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="Provides +1 [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness for every 2 [ICON_CULTURE] Social Policies you have adopted."/>
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_EIFFEL_TOWER_HELP" />
	</Update>

	<Update>
		<Set Text="Each source of [ICON_RES_IRON] Iron or [ICON_RES_COPPER] Copper worked by this City produces +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have a mined source of [ICON_RES_IRON] Iron or [ICON_RES_COPPER] Copper nearby."/>
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FORGE_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="10% of [ICON_FOOD] Food is carried over after a new [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizen is born. +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold in every tile next to a River.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must be built next to a River.[NEWLINE]City must have a Sewer System."/>
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_AQUEDUCT_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="+2 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture per turn from [ICON_RES_INCENSE] Incense and +2 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture from [ICON_RES_WINE] Grapes nearby.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have an improved source of at least one of these resources nearby." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MONASTERY_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="+1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science for every 2 [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizens in this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Must have built a Library in all Cities. The cost goes up the more cities there are in the empire." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NATIONAL_COLLEGE_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="Massively increases [ICON_FOOD] Food production in the city in which this is built." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_TEMPLE_ARTEMIS_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production in every tile next to a River.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Requires 1 [ICON_RES_ALUMINUM] Aluminum for Construction.[NEWLINE]City must be built next to a River." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HYDRO_PLANT_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="+2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold from water tiles worked by this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must be built on the coast." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_COLOSSUS_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production from Engineer Specialists in every City.[NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold from Merchant Specialists in every City.[NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science from Scientist Specialist and Artist Specialist in every City." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_STATUE_OF_LIBERTY_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="+1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science for every 2 [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizens in this City." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LIBRARY_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="+1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science for every 2 [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizens in this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have a University." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_PUBLIC_SCHOOL_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="City must have a Public School." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LABORATORY_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="+2 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science from Jungle tiles worked by this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have a Library." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_UNIVERSITY_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="Significantly increases [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production in this City. Provides 4 [ICON_POWER3] Electricity.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Requires a nearby desert for construction. City must have a Factory." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SOLAR_PLANT_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="Requires 1 [ICON_POWER3] Electricity for construction." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FACTORY_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="Cities constructed on hills may not build Windmills." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WINDMILL_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="+1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold from Merchant Specialists in every City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Requires Markets in every City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Cost increases for each additional City." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NATIONAL_TREASURY_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="+1 [ICON_FOOD] Food from Water Tiles. +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food from Sea Resources worked by this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must be built on the coast." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_LIGHTHOUSE_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<!--<Update>
			<Set Text="+15 XP for Naval Units produced in this City. Forms a [ICON_CONNECTED] Trade Route with the [ICON_CAPITAL] Capital over water (if they're not already [ICON_CONNECTED] connected by land).[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must be built on the coast." />
			<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HARBOR_HELP" />
		</Update>-->
	<Update>
		<Set Text="+1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold from Water Tiles.[NEWLINE]+1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production from Sea Resources worked by this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have a Harbor." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SEAPORT_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="City must be built next to a River." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WATERMILL_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="Required for Supercarrier, A-Bomb, Nuclear Missile, and Nuclear Submarine production. Provides 14 [ICON_POWER3] Electricity [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have a Factory. Requires 2 [ICON_RES_URANIUM] Uranium." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_NUCLEAR_PLANT_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="City must be built within 2 tiles of a Mountain." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_OBSERVATORY_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="10% of [ICON_FOOD] Food is carried over after a new [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizen is born." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HOSPITAL_STRATEGY" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="Each source of [ICON_RES_URANIUM] Uranium worked by this City produces +3 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have a Hospital." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_MEDICAL_LAB_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="All newly-trained Units in this City receive the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Morale[ENDCOLOR] Promotion, improving [ICON_STRENGTH] combat strength by 15%.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Must have built a Barracks in all Cities.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE] May build up to 1." />
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HEROIC_EPIC_HELP" />
	</Update>

	<!--BUILDINGS-->
	<!--ANCIENT-->


	<!--UPDATE-->

	<Update>
		<Set Text="+2 [ICON_FOOD] Food from every Oasis."/>
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BAZAAR_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="+2 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science from Jungle tiles worked by this City.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have a Library."/>
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WAT_HELP" />
	</Update>


	<!--ANCIENT
		-->




	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BREWERY</Tag>
		<Text>Brewery</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BREWERY_PEDIA</Tag>
		<Text>A brewery is a dedicated building for the making of beer, though beer can be made at home, and has been for much of beer's history. A company which makes beer is called either a brewery or a brewing company.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The diversity of size in breweries is matched by the diversity of processes, degrees of automation, and kinds of beer produced in breweries. Typically a brewery is divided into distinct sections, with each section reserved for one part of the brewing process.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BREWERY_HELP</Tag>
		<Text>Provides two resources of [ICON_RES_BBER] Beer. Need to [ICON_RES_WHEAT] Wheat and [ICON_RES_BARLEY] Barley to be build. Each source of [ICON_RES_SUGAR] Sugar, [ICON_RES_SPICES] Spices, [ICON_RES_CITRUS] Citrus, or [ICON_BARLEY] Barley worked by this City produce +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have an improved source of one of these resources nearby.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BREWERY_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<Text>The Brewery increases the [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness in the empire and boost the city's growth by boosting the food output of many resources. It's useful if you want to grow your city.</Text>
	</Row>
	
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BURIAL_MOUND</Tag>
		<Text>Burial Mound</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BURIAL_MOUND_PEDIA</Tag>
		<Text>Burial Mounds are a type of monumental architecture built primarily of earth, although they do occasionally have stone or wood foundations. These structures may or may not contain human burials.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Burial Mounds have been used for thousands of years as a both a function of spiritual rites, as well as more pragmatic protection against disease and vermin.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BURIAL_MOUND_STRATEGY</Tag>
		<Text>The Burial Mound increases the Culture of a city, speeding the growth of the city's territory.</Text>
	</Row>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="Each source of [ICON_RES_FUR] Fur and [ICON_RES_IVORY] Ivory worked by this City produce +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have an improved source of [ICON_RES_HORSE] Horses, [ICON_RES_FUR] Fur, or [ICON_RES_IVORY] Ivory nearby."/>
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_CIRCUS_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="+10% [ICON_FOOD] Food carried over after a [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizen is born."/>
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GRANARY_HELP" />
	</Update>
	<Update>
		<Set Text="Each source of [ICON_RES_MARBLE] Marble worked by this City produce +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have an improved source of [ICON_RES_MARBLE] Marble, [ICON_RES_STONE] Stone, or [ICON_RES_JADE] Jade nearby.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must not be in Plains."/>
		<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_STONE_WORKS_HELP" />
	</Update>

	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FUSION_LAB">
		<Text>Fusion Lab</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FUSION_LAB_HEADING">
		<Text>Fusion Lab</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FUSION_LAB_QUOTE">
		<Text>[NEWLINE][TAB][TAB]"It will happen, and it will happen in our lifetimes. Fusion Power isn't just the future. Fusion Power is now."[NEWLINE][TAB][TAB] - T.M. Morgan-Reilly,[NEWLINE][TAB][TAB][TAB] Morgan Metagenics [NEWLINE][TAB]</Text>
	</Row>
	<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FUSION_LAB_HELP">
		<Text>Increase the [ICON_RESEARCH] Science output of this city by +15%.[NEWLINE]Requires 5 [ICON_POWER3] Electricity to be build.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]City must have a Research Laboratory.</Text>
	</Row>
</Language_en_US>
	<!--Have a nice day:=)-->
</GameData>